(lyrics)
（歌词）
Hi guys.
嗨，大家好。
Hold up.
耽误。
Let me turn the music down a little bit.
让我把音乐调小一点。
Everybody. What's up.
大家。 怎么了。
Good evening. Good morning.
晚上好。 早上好。
Hope a lot of people.
希望很多人。
didn't have to wake up too early
for this as well, but.
也不必为此起得太早，但是。
Hey. Hi, everybody.
嘿。 大家好你们好。
Hope you're having a good day so far.
希望到目前为止你过得愉快。
It's been a little bit,
but I've been working hard.
有一点点，但我一直在努力。
I've been working
really, really hard for the stream.
我一直非常非常努力地工作。
Because, you know,
I've wanted to really make sure
因为，你知道，我真的想确定
I knew how to do some of these songs.
我知道如何演奏其中一些歌曲。
So that's why, you know, I spent.
所以这就是为什么，你知道，我花了。
Pretty much all.
几乎所有。
Day today and all day yesterday doing
what's it called?
今天一天一天昨天一天都在做什么，这叫什么？
Just practising a bunch of songs
只是练习了一堆歌曲
Umm,for the stream.
嗯，为了流。
I am going to have sound
我将关闭声音警报和通知，以便，
alerts and notifications off in order to,
you know, just make sure there's
no interruptions during the stream.
你知道，只要确保直播期间没有中断。
But I will probably be doing
a reading for all of the
但我可能会阅读所有的
for all the donations and
感谢你们在我们唱完卡拉OK后发送的所有捐款和任何其他信息，好吗？
any other messages
you guys send after we do our karaoke, OK?
So we'll have a bit of an.
所以我们会有一点。
After party and then just chill and chat
once the karaoke is over.
派对结束后，卡拉 OK 结束后就放松和聊天。
If that sounds good to you guys.
如果这对你们来说听起来不错。
All right.
好的。
Yeah, we are.
是的，我们是。
And I'm so nervous.
我很紧张。
I don't know why. I've done karaokes before,
but I think it's.
我不知道为什么。 我以前做过卡拉OK，但我认为是。
Just because, like,
只是因为，比如，
I don't know, there's just so much more
so many more of you guys around now.
我不知道，现在你们身边还有这么多这么多的人。
That makes it.
这样就可以了。
All the more like my heart
is going really fast.
更像是我的心跳得非常快。
Right now.
现在。
Like, if I had the microphone the yes on
my microphone, I could let you guys hear.
就像，如果我有麦克风，我的麦克风上有“是”，我可以让你们听到。
Actually, I do, but. I don't think
I want to do that. Right now.
其实我有，但是。 我不认为我想这样做。 现在。
It's gone.
它不见了。
Ba dum ba dum ba dum, ba dum, ba dum.
巴达姆巴达姆巴达姆，巴达姆，巴达姆。
And and my hands are,
you know, I'm doing the thing
而且我的手，你知道，当我紧张的时候，我会揉腿。
where when I get nervous,
I, like, rub my legs.
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I don't know why.
我不知道为什么。
It's like the nerves are getting to me
right now, but I think, like, once
就好像我现在很紧张，但我想，就像，一旦你进入歌曲，一切都会好起来的。
you get into the songs, it'll be OK.
Yeah, we've done
是的，我们以前做过卡拉OK，但它只是，你知道，我是。
karaoke before, but it's just,
you know, I'm.
I'm. I'm shy of it from time to time,
I guess.
我是。 我想我有时会害羞。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm just the.
我只是。
Ignore me in my, you know, nerves
getting all over the place.
忽略我，你知道，我的神经到处都是。
But, yeah. I
但是，是的。 一世
I think I have.
我想我有。
Quite a few songs that I just want to sing
that are kind of new.
有几首我只想唱的歌曲是新的。
And there's some there's going to be
some old ones returning,
还有一些会有一些旧的回来，
but I'm OK with taking song requests
in, in between songs, but,
但我可以在歌曲之间接受歌曲请求，但是，你知道，只是不要在歌曲期间提出请求。
you know, just don't request it
during the songs.
When I'm done with a song.
当我唱完一首歌。
In between, we can talk.
中间可以聊聊。
And then if you have a request,
that's something I know I can't promise
如果你有要求，我知道我不能保证
I can do like a song that, ah,
what's that?
我可以像一首歌那样，啊，那是什么？
I can't promise that I can do a song
我不能保证我会做一首歌
that you
want me to do because I may not know it.
你想让我做的，因为我可能不知道。
Right? I can, I can
对？ 我可以，我可以尝试，如果我知道这首歌，但喜欢。
attempt to,
if I know the song though, but like.
Yeah.
是的。
But, oh dude, I,
但是，哦，伙计，我，
I'm so excited because this is a big.
我很兴奋，因为这是一个很大的。
Celebration for a really big milestone
that we hit on the channel.
庆祝我们在频道上取得的一个非常重要的里程碑。
300 K on Twitch is no joke, guys.
伙计们，Twitch 上的 300 K 可不是开玩笑的。
That's a lot of people and it's a
那是很多人，这甚至让你知道，更疯狂。
make even like, you know, more crazy.
It's over that over
before I drink on Twitter
在我在 Twitter 和 YouTube
and on YouTube,
we're almost at 400 as well like that.
上喝酒之前，一切都结束了，我们差不多是 400 岁。
There's a lot happening.
有很多事情发生。
There's a lot, a lot happening
and I got a lot of plans
有很多很多的事情发生，我有很多计划，就像新的一样，有很多事情即将发生，我希望
and there's like new there's
so much coming down the line and I hope
everyone's excited for it
cause I am super stoked for everything
每个人都为此感到兴奋，因为我对即将发生的一切感到非常兴奋
that's going to be happening
Congratulations on all the followers.
祝贺所有的追随者。
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢你。 非常感谢。
Congrats. Congrats.
恭喜。 恭喜。
Thank you, guys.
谢谢你们。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Why I was so nervous today, ah but
为什么我今天这么紧张，啊，但只是要摆脱紧张。 肖战，摆脱紧张。
just got to shake off the nervous.
Shoto, shake off the nervous.
It's. It'll be okay.
它的。 会好的。
Is my throat OK?
我的喉咙好吗？
Yeah, my throat is OK. Yesterday, I.
是的，我的喉咙没问题。 昨天我。
Kind of overdid it
because I realised, like,
有点过头了，因为我意识到，就像，它变得非常刺耳，但我睡觉时开着加湿器
it got really raspy,
but I slept with my humidifier on and
gave it some proper rest in the morning
before I practise again.
早上在我再次练习之前给了​​它一些适当的休息。
So I think I'm pretty. Yeah, pretty good.
所以我觉得我很漂亮。 是的，很不错。
I feel I am pretty good.
我觉得我还不错。
I don't think there's going
to be any problems, but I know my limits,
我不认为会有任何问题，但我知道我的极限，所以不要担心。
so don't worry.
I will be able to.
我将能。
I'll stop when I feel like it's too much.
当我觉得它太多时，我会停下来。
But usually I can handle what my throat is
a, you know, a sturdy boy.
但通常我可以应付我的喉咙是一个，你知道的，一个强壮的男孩。
He's got it.
他明白了。
But hopefully.
但希望如此。
Everyone's been having a wonderful week
so far.
到目前为止，每个人都度过了美好的一周。
It's already Friday.
已经是星期五了。
It's Saturday for some of you.
对于你们中的一些人来说，今天是星期六。
Saturday morning, I think an hour
or about to head into another week.
星期六早上，我想一个小时或即将进入另一个星期。
It's it's almost may believe that
April is already almost over and then.
几乎可以相信四月已经快结束了。
We're heading into another month of spring
and then summer's coming down the line.
我们正在进入另一个春天的月份，然后夏天即将来临。
And man, it's crazy, guys.
伙计们，这太疯狂了。
Like we're
almost to the halfway point for the year
就像我们快到今年的一半了
it's it's a really fucking crazy dude,
这是一个非常他妈的疯狂的家伙，但我为即将到来的一切感到兴奋。
but I'm excited for everything
that's coming.
And like I said before, hopefully
就像我之前说的，希望你这一周过得很好，每个人都过得很好
your week's been good
and everyone's doing well
for your exams
because I know it's a busy exam period.
为你的考试，因为我知道这是一个繁忙的考试时期。
So. So, like I said, Livestream,
you got this.
所以。 所以，就像我说的，Livestream，你明白了。
All right?
Don't don't stress out too much over it.
好的？ 不要过分强调它。
Just take it easy and, like, don't,
you know, cram everything.
放轻松，就像，不要，你知道的，把所有东西都塞进去。
You'll be fine.
你会好起来的。
Lots of people are still doing exams,
but if you.
很多人还在做考试，但如果你。
Finish your exams,
hey, pog, you're done, GG, guys.
完成你的考试，嘿，pog，你已经完成了，GG，伙计们。
You made it
你在年底到达院子，享受你的暑假。
to the yards at the end of the year
and gets enjoy your summer vacation break.
Right. I'll I think a lot of.
对。 我会想很多。
People get to enjoy their breaks now
since they're done with school.
人们现在可以享受假期了，因为他们完成了学业。
OK, but I think.
好的，但我认为。
We can probably head into the first song
just to, like,
我们可能可以进入第一首歌，就像，
you know, get things, you know, break,
break the ice for tonight.
你知道，拿东西，你知道，打破，打破今晚的僵局。
Guessing are an old favourite of mine
I've done on the channel
猜测是我在频道上做过的最喜欢的事情
quite a few times,
but I'm not like all the time,
很多次，但我不是一直都喜欢，但我很喜欢这首歌
but I like the song a lot
and if you guys want to guess,
you guys want to guess what song it is.
如果你们想猜，你们就想猜它是什么歌。
It's something we've seen before, so
这是我们以前见过的东西，所以可能不会太令人惊讶。
probably not too much of a surprise mm.
Lemon.
柠檬。
No, not lemon.
不，不是柠檬。
Oh, give me a second.
哦，给我一秒钟。
Wait a second. What's happening?
等一下。 怎么了？
Oh, no. Oh,
不好了。 哦，
oh, God.
天啊。
Internet
互联网
oh, no way.
哦，没办法。
Internet.
互联网。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Oh, no. Oh.
不好了。 哦。
Oh, god. OK.
天啊。 好的。
All Oh, shit.
哦，狗屎。
Oh, fuck, dude.
哦，操，伙计。
Really?
真的吗？
Ah, I think. I'm.
啊，我想。 我是。
Ah. It seems that there is some lag. Hmm.
啊。 似乎有一些滞后。 唔。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I think it might get better.
我想它可能会好起来。
Hopefully that was temporary
希望那是暂时的
yeah.
是的。
Hopefully it's back now. Oh, my God.
希望它现在回来了。 我的天啊。
I don't know what that was.
我不知道那是什么。
Mm. Is it butter?
毫米。 是黄油吗？
I think it's better now. Oh, jeez.
我觉得现在好多了。 哦，天哪。
Oh, jeez.
哦，天哪。
It's like. Uh.
它像是。 呃。
Can you guys hear me?
你们能听到我吗？
Is everything back
where we were chillin or die?
一切都回到了我们寒冷或死亡的地方吗？
Jobs.
工作。
Are things ok?
事情还好吗？
OK, yeah.
好的，是的。
Just be sure to.
一定要。
Refresh the stream. Hold on. Let me check
刷新流。 坚持，稍等。 让我检查
to make sure that everything's good.
以确保一切正常。
I hope. I hope.
我希望。 我希望。
And and
这不是今晚再次愚蠢，因为如果那样的话，我会非常难过。
that's not being dumb again tonight,
because if it is then I would be very sad.
I could. Yeah.
我可以。 是的。
Just refresh on if everything's OK.
如果一切正常，请刷新。
If it's a bit laggy.
如果有点拖沓。
I think it's good now.
我觉得现在很好。
I think it was just a temporary hiccup.
我想这只是一个暂时的小插曲。
We cool now?
我们现在冷静吗？
OK, yeah.
好的，是的。
We'll wait a little bit
until everyone, like,
我们会等一会儿，直到每个人，比如，你知道，每个人都再次稳定下来，因为。
you know, everyone stabilises again
because.
I think that was just a.
我认为那只是一个。
Little you know, we're a little
你知道的很少，我们有点
kind of.
有点儿。
Just just a small. Blip.
只是一个小。 昙花一现。
Don't know why that happened, though.
不知道为什么会这样。
I think we're good now. Yeah.
我认为我们现在很好。 是的。
Yeah, sorry about that.
是的，对此感到抱歉。
I don't know why that happened.
我不知道为什么会这样。
Hmm. That's odd.
唔。 这很奇怪。
Well, hopefully that doesn't happen
好吧，希望这不会在剩下的晚上发生，因为如果它看起来。
for the rest of the night,
because if it and look.
Well, I'm gonna.
嗯，我会的。
I'm going to eat Comcast's.
我要去吃康卡斯特的。
Arse. OK?
屁股。 好的？
But a lot of you are saying quite it's.
但是你们中的很多人都说它是。
Did I really think that that much?
我真的想那么多吗？
I do. To be honest. You're right.
我愿意。 老实说。 你说的对。
But no. We're not singing that one today.
但不是。 我们今天不唱那首。
Um, yeah.
嗯，是的。
Hold on. Give me a second. I'm gonna
坚持，稍等。 你稍等一会儿。 我将要
find the lyrics for it right now.
立即找到它的歌词。
Because I didn't pull up the lyrics
like a smart move.
因为我没有像一个聪明的举动那样拉起歌词。
Why don't I do that beforehand?
为什么我不事先这样做？
Hold on. OK.
坚持，稍等。 好的。
All right.
好的。
There it is.
它在那里。
All right, here we go.
好吧，我们开始吧。
For some of the night
对于某些夜晚
now was my. Heart, dude.
现在是我的。 心脏，伙计。
My heart needs to get it
under control. Ah,
我的心需要得到控制。 啊，
all right.
好的。
私は私
我只是我，
貴方は貴方と
你只是你
昨夜言ってた そんな気もする
我昨晚说过，现在还是一样
わ~~
~~
グレイのジャケットに
你穿着灰色夹克，
見覚えがある
上面沾着熟悉的
コーヒーのしみ
相変らずなのね
和往常一样
ショーウィンドウに
我们在橱窗里
二人映れば
二人的倒影
stay with me
留在我身边
真夜中のドアをたたき
半夜敲门,求你别回家
帰らないでと泣いた
在你眼前哭泣的
あの季節が 今 目の前
那个季节
Stay with me 口ぐせを言いながら
留在我身边 说我们最喜欢的话，
二人の瞬間を
抓住我们的小美好
抱いて
小确幸
まだ忘れず 大事に
只要我活着，我就永远不会忘记它
していた
不会忘记
恋と愛とは
他们说爱和亲情是
違うものだよと
两种不同的东西
昨夜言われた
你昨晚告诉我的
そんな気もするわ
有时候我也这么想
二度目の冬が来て
冬天又来了，你的心已经远去
離れていった貴方の心
如果我回头看
ふり返ればいつも
我总能感觉到
そこに 貴方を
你在
感じていたの
我身边
Stay with me
留在我身边
真夜中のドアを
敲半夜的门，
たたき 心に穴が
心里有个空虚的洞
あいた
在你眼前
あの季節が
哭泣的那个季节
今 目の前 stay with me
留在我身边...
口ぐせを言いながら
被我的孤独淹没，唱机上的针卡在重复的旋律上
二人の瞬間を抱いて
抓住我们的小美好
まだ忘れず
我永远不会忘记
暖めてた
那种温暖的感觉
まだ忘れず 大事にしていた
只要我活着，我就永远不会忘记它
oh! Uh.
哦！ 呃。
shake off nervous, Shoto.
摆脱紧张，Shoto。
Come on, it's not that bad.
来吧，这不是那么糟糕。
Oh, my God I feel I feel like I of.
哦，我的天哪，我觉得我感觉像我。
Bruh ruh ruh ruh.
布鲁鲁哈鲁哈鲁。
I got.
我有。
I got real nervous during that one, bros.
那段时间我真的很紧张，兄弟们。
Damn, I think I fumbled a lyric or two,
but that's OK.
该死的，我想我摸索了一两句歌词，但没关系。
That's OK.
那没问题。
So yeah,
that was the first song of the night.
所以，是的，那是当晚的第一首歌。
Stay with. Me. It's uhm.
留下来。 我。 嗯。
I only.
我只是。
Got in so like,
you know, city pop not too long ago,
不久前就加入了城市流行音乐，但由于城市流行音乐，它很快成为我的最爱之一。
but it quickly became one of my favourites
because of the city pop.
or Japanese pop genre and God it is,
或日本流行音乐类型，它是，
it's such a beautiful song.
这是一首美丽的歌。
I always go back to it
whenever I want it, you know, just
我总是在我想要的时候回到它，你知道，只是
like the original song.
喜欢原曲。
I like the guitar version
or anything like the O.G version.
我喜欢吉他版或OG版之类的。
It's so fucking good and I recommend
people listen to the full thing
太好了，我建议人们听完整的东西
if they haven't before.
如果他们以前没有。
I'm glad you guys liked it.
我很高兴你们喜欢它。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Like I said before, I.
就像我之前说的，我。
Will read through the donas.
将通读捐赠。
All of the gift, subs, and bits after
卡拉 OK 结束后的所有礼物、订阅和比特。 好的。
the karaoke session is over. OK.
I promise I will
我保证我会
I love you guys.
我爱你们。
I'm glad everyone was able to,
我很高兴每个人都能，你知道，今天过来并为此腾出时间，因为。
you know, come by today
and make time for this because.
嗯
I really.
我真的。
Wanted to do something special.
想做一些特别的事情。
As a, you know, as a celebration stream
for a
作为一个，你知道的，作为一个庆祝活动
for this milestone.
对于这个里程碑。
And I thought, you know,
I think another like
我想，你知道，我认为另一个像
alcohol, whatever, one shot, one screams,
everything would just be like, yeah.
酒精，随便啦，尖叫，一切都会像，是的。
But I think the best way I can do it
但我认为我能做到的最好方法
is by sharing something
that is really precious to me
是通过分享对我来说非常珍贵的东西
and something that I feel like
is probably my most prised.
我觉得可能是我最珍惜的东西。
Oh, I don't know.
哦我不知道。
In most
多数情况
the thing
I'm like most shy about my singing.
我最害羞的就是我的歌声。
Like, I fully believe that anybody
就像，我完全相信任何人
who shares their singing voice
with the world or like any other person
谁与世界分享他们的歌声，或者像任何其他人一样，或者就像另一个朋友或个人一样，这是非常特别的事情。
or just like another of friends or an
individual, it's something very special.
Singing and hearing somebody like
唱歌和听别人喜欢
their own
singing is something magical to me.
他们自己的歌声对我来说很神奇。
And that's. Why. I.
就是这样。 为什么。 一世。
I feel like
我觉得像
hearing being like, graced
with somebody else's voice when they sing
听到别人唱歌时听到别人的声音就像是最高荣誉之一，我想，对我来说。
a song is like one of the highest honours,
I guess, to me.
So that's why when people had their
first time karaoke is
所以这就是为什么当人们第一次唱卡拉OK时
like, you know, my other friends did.
就像，你知道的，我的其他朋友做过。
It was just.
这只是。
It made me smile.
It made me smile so much.
它让我微笑。 这让我笑了很多。
And I really hope I get to hear
more people who haven't sing, sung
我真的希望我能听到更多没有唱歌的人
Yeah.
是的。
We're
going to be drinking some alcohol later,
我们稍后要喝点酒，但我没有，我在附近的冰箱里有一些
but I don't have
I have some in the fridge nearby
so. Yeah, that was.
所以。 是的，那是。
Stay with me
留在我身边
I hope you guys enjoyed that
我希望你们喜欢
So this next Song
所以这下一首歌
I wanted.
我想了。
To talk a bit before we sing the song.
在我们唱这首歌之前先谈谈。
It's been.
它是。
It's been wonderful.
这太棒了。
And I have.
我有。
Loved every moment we've
爱我们的每一刻
gone to share together on our adventure.
一起去分享我们的冒险经历。
And the reason why I started this guild
以及我成立这个公会的原因
and the reason why I'm here with you all
我现在和你们在一起的原因是因为对朋友的承诺
now is because of a promise
to a friend and
a friend.
一个朋友。
It's a friend who was lost long ago.
这是一个很久以前失去的朋友。
Many, along with many others from my home,
许多，以及我家中的许多其他人，
we promised each other to see the world
to go on many adventures to soar,
我们彼此许诺要看到这个世界继续进行许多冒险翱翔，精灵的蓝天乘船进入东方沿海水域。
the blue skies of elves on ships
into coastal waters of the east.
But and we wanted to do it all together.
但是，我们想一起做这一切。
Hand in hand. And that was our dream. But
手牵手。 那是我们的梦想。 但
he's not with me anymore.
他不再和我在一起了。
And since that day, our
从那天起，我们的
since I'd say I was
因为我会说我迷路了，困惑了，而且。
lost, confused, and.
And I didn't know what to have my.
我不知道该拥有什么。
Myself.
我。
I had no one,
and I lost everything I cared for.
我没有人，我失去了我在乎的一切。
But being in this guild with all of you
但是和你们所有人一起在这个公会中并继续
and continuing to
grow and rebuild
成长和重建这个家庭，我曾经失去过
this family, I once lost
has been the most surreal journey.
一直是最超现实的旅程。
And I promised Aether
that I would see the world with him.
我向Aether保证我会和他一起看世界。
But now I carry on that promise
但现在我继续承诺
to you guys and to myself.
对你们和我自己。
And I vow to journey forever and ever.
我发誓要永远旅行。
As long as my soul continues to burn.
只要我的灵魂继续燃烧。
As long as my legs can stand.
只要我的腿能站起来。
And as long as you all
will stay by my side.
只要你们都留在我身边。
I mean, I just want to adventure
and carry on his wish
我的意思是，我只想冒险并继续他的愿望，不仅是为了我们俩，也是为了我和我的公会。
for not only the both of us,
but for me and my guilds.
Like,
像，
I'm your guild leader and it's been
我是你们的公会领袖
it's been the greatest honour
能成为这样的人是世界上最大的荣幸
in the world to be someone that
to be someone that you can look up to,
成为一个你可以仰望的人，成为一个可以激励的人
to be someone to inspire
and to laugh with and
和一起笑
I promise
我保证
I promise to take you
我保证带走我的公会，
my guildies,
that as long as you're with me
只要你和我在一起
and as long as you're with the Guild,
只要你和公会在一起，
no, I will continue to do my best
不，我会继续努力
and make this an unforgettable journey.
并让这成为一次难忘的旅程。
An unforgettable journey to remember
一段难忘的旅程，让你终生难忘。
for the rest of your lives.
And I. I
而我。我
I want to hold.
我想抱。
On to this feeling you've given me.
关于你给我的这种感觉。
And I never wants these journeys to end.
我从不希望这些旅程结束。
And I'm prepared
我准备好对付最强的老板，
to take on the strongest of bosses,
the most difficult of rides.
最困难的游乐设施。
And I sound like it and the most
我听起来最喜欢
intimidating of our worlds.
恐吓我们的世界。
Unknowns in order to keep doing
what I'm doing with you all
未知数，以便尽可能长时间地继续与你们一起做我正在做的事情，而我只是。
now for as long as I can and I just.
I really want to try.
我真的很想试试。
I really just wanna try
我真的只想试试
So thank you all
所以感谢你们让我成为世界上最快乐的男孩。
for making me
the happiest boy in the world.
Really?
真的吗？
I can't.
我不能。
I can't thank you enough for that.
我不能为此感谢你。
And for helping me fulfil my promise
为了帮助我实现我的承诺
The next song
I wanted to sing captures that
我想唱的下一首歌就是这样
this feeling that I've been holding on
since the very beginning
这种感觉从一开始就一直坚持，自从我们一起踏上这段旅程以来。
and since we've gone on this journey
together.
And it's called The Promise of the World.
它被称为世界的约定。
It's from Howl's Moving Castle.
它来自哈尔的移动城堡。
I think a few of you might know it
我想你们中的一些人可能知道
I've never sung this before.
我以前从来没有唱过这个。
I've tried to practise, and I hope it goes
well.
我已经尝试过练习，希望一切顺利。
I'm OK.
我很好。
I gotta look up the lyrics.
我得查歌词。
There it is.
它在那里。
You're so dumb shoto.
你真是个笨蛋。
涙の奥に
在你泪水深处
~
ゆらぐほほえみは
颤抖的微笑
~
時の始めからの
是世界从时间
世界の
开始的
約束
诺言
~
いまは一人
即使我现在一个人，
でも二人の昨日
从我们的昨天开始
から 今日
今天仍然闪闪发光
は生まれきらめく
就像我们第一次见面的
初めて会った日のように
那天一样
~
思い出のう
你不在
ちに
我的
あなたはいない
记忆里
~
そよかぜとなって
你化作微风
頬に触れてくる
抚摸我的脸颊
~
（るるるら~）
木漏れ日の午後の
即使在我们下午离别之后，
別れのあとも
阳光透过树林照耀着
決して
世界的承诺
終わらない
永远不会结束
世界
の約束.
的承诺。
いまは一人
就算我现在一个人
でも
但
明日は限りない
明天是无限的
あなたが
你教会了我关于
教えてくれた
潜伏在
夜にひそむ
夜里的
やさしさ
温柔
思い出のうちに
你不在
あなたはい
我的
ない
记忆里
せせらぎの
所以永远活在
歌に
溪流的歌声中
この空の色に
在这天空的颜色里，
花の香りに
在花的芬芳里
いつまでも生きて
生生不息
~huh
~呵呵
oh, god.
天啊。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
I yeah.
我是的。
That's a apologise there.
那是一个道歉。
I think I. Almost ah, I think I was, I was.
我想我。差不多啊，我想我是，我是。
Holding back a little bit
because I told myself I wouldn't.
有点退缩，因为我告诉自己我不会。
Cry.
哭。
oh, I'm sorry.
哦，对不起。
God.
上帝。
I really don't appreciate you guys a lot,
so thank you for being here
我真的不太感谢你们，所以感谢你们的光临
and for
for holding
因为我兑现了我很久以前对我朋友的承诺。
that promise I made long ago to my friend.
It means a lot.
那意义重大。
So yeah, that was
所以，是的，那是世界的承诺。
that was a promise of the world.
It's a song
这是一首歌
composed by, you know,  Hisaishi Jō.
由久石让作曲。
It's from, from
它来自，来自
it's a Ghibli song from Howl's
Moving Castle, and it's
这是哈尔的移动城堡中的一首歌曲，它是
something
I think fondly about long ago. And
很久以前我就很喜欢的事情。 和
it has a
它对我有一种怀旧的感觉，直到我听它的时候
sense of nostalgia to me
til when I when I listen to it
and I finally got to learn it
and share it with you guys.
我终于学会了它并与大家分享。
And I'm happy that I did
I hope you enjoyed it.
我很高兴我做到了希望你喜欢它。
I didn't butcher anything.
我没有屠宰任何东西。
I think I did. But
我想我做到了。 但
muah,
嗯，谢谢各位。
thank you guys.
Ah.
啊。
So let me add that to the list that was
所以让我把它添加到列表中
promise of the world. OK?
世界的承诺。 好的？
OK. It was
好的。 它是
I was just a little
a little shaky there, but
我只是有点摇摇欲坠，但是
then I just.
然后我只是。
The song is a lot.
这首歌很多。
More like beautiful.
更喜欢美丽。
I thought when I actually got to sing it
我想当我真的要唱它并且喜欢时，你知道，通过歌词学习我的节奏。
and like, you know, go through the lyrics
and learn my flow with it.
I've.
我有。
I've known the song for a long time
because I was moving.
我很早就知道这首歌了，因为我在动。
Castle used to be part of my,
you know, childhood.
城堡曾经是我童年的一部分。
I love that movie.
我喜欢那部电影。
And I love the
you know, I love Ghibli films a lot.
我爱你知道的，我非常喜欢宫崎骏的电影。
So I guess it's there's a difference
between just listening to it
所以我想只是听它和学习歌曲和学习歌词和喜欢学习是有区别的
and learning the songs
and learning the lyrics and like learning
the flow of it with the in like,
you know, tandem with the instrumental.
它的流动与 in 类似，你知道，与乐器串联。
It's really beautiful.
它真的很漂亮。
And and I think I really don't want to.
而且我想我真的不想。
It feel, It makes me feel
感觉，这让我觉得我想学习更多的歌曲，我猜是因为那里没有很好的解释。
like I want to learn more songs, I guess
for lack of a good explanation there.
I think this one
of all the ones that I practise
我认为这是我练习的所有方法之一
was the
是
was that really pushed me
to get more motivation
是不是真的让我有了更多的动力去唱更多的新歌和你们分享
to sing some more new songs
and share with you guys
oh, OK.
哦好的。
Yeah, that was Promise of the World.
是的，那是世界的承诺。
I love you so much.
我真的很爱你。
I love you guys too.
我也爱你们。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
It's like it's very warm.
好像很暖和。
And comforting to have them.
并安慰拥有它们。
You know, the company of my guildies here.
你知道，我的公会在这里。
It's like, you know, cheer me on when.
就像，你知道的，在什么时候为我加油。
I like I was.
我喜欢我。
Really nervous even yesterday.
昨天还真的很紧张。
Two days ago, I think that's.
两天前，我认为是。
When the nerves started hitting.
And I don't know why.
当神经开始受到打击。 同时我不知道为什么。
I guess, like,
我想，就像我之前说的，只是想到有这么多新的公会成员。
like I said before, it's just the thought
of there being so many new guild members.
And, you know, the fact that I'm just
而且，你知道，事实上我只是
there's a lot of new songs still,
and it's like, out of my comfort zone.
仍然有很多新歌，这就像，超出了我的舒适区。
Which is really making me
这真的让我
but it means a lot that you all are here.
但这意味着你们所有人都在这里。
Like, I don't know what I would do
if I don't have my guildies
就像，如果我没有我的行会来支持我，我不知道我会怎么做。 和
there to support me. And
you guys're always still, as always still.
你们总是静止的，一如既往的静止。
And I give back. OK?
我回馈。 好的？
But for my next song,
但对于我的下一首歌，
I think I'm going to do another good
我想我会做另一件好事，做另一件你们很多人都熟悉的事。
do another one
that's familiar to a lot of you guys.
It's uh. it's another city pop song.
是啊。 这是另一首城市流行歌曲。
You guys want to take a guess?
大家想猜一猜吗？
you wanna take a guess or what it is?
你想猜一猜还是它是什么？
It's I guess.
我猜是这样。
I've done it before multiple times as well
我之前也做过很多次
as solitary.
作为孤独。
Just that.
只是。
Dude, I. Wish I could do right on time.
伙计，我希望我能按时做对。
Oh, my God. Right on time
is such an amazing song.
我的天啊。 准时是这样一首令人惊叹的歌曲。
Ah, I tried practising it, but.
啊，我试过练习它，但是。
I didn't have enough time.
我没有足够的时间。
I felt like and it's like.
我觉得和它是一样的。
If I want to do it right.
如果我想做正确的事。
I got to do it right, you know? So
我必须做对，你知道吗？ 所以
maybe, maybe another,
也许，也许另一个，另一个时间，在不久的将来的另一天。
another time for another day
in the near future.
I can learn right on time.
我可以按时学习。
Right on time.
准时。
Not bad up, but da da da da.
还不错，但是哒哒哒哒。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
So your next.
所以你的下一个。
One is.
一个是。
If you put it on before we sing it
如果你在我们唱歌之前戴上它
Plus the glove.
加上手套。
Yeah.
是的。
On my favourites.
在我的最爱。
I I think my top to say
我认为我最喜欢说流行歌曲是塑料手套的末端
pop songs are plastic glove ends on
and stay with me
和我在一起
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Thank you so much for all the donations,
guys, and for the gifts subs.
非常感谢你们所有的捐款，伙计们，还有礼物订阅。
I promise I'll get to it after we're done.
我保证在我们完成后我会去做。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
Yes, a second.
是的，一秒钟。
Plastic love
塑料爱情
Here we go.
开始了。
hum hum hum
哼哼哼哼
bala bala bababa
巴拉巴拉巴巴巴
OK.
好的。
Still nervous, but
还是很紧张，但是
we got the this.
我们得到了这个。
We got this.
bara
bara barabab do bam~
barabab do bam~
突然の
可别因为
キスや
突如其来的kiss
~
熱いまなざしで
或是火热的眼神
恋のプロ
就让恋爱
グラムを
的节拍
~
狂わせないでね
崩溃掉哦
出逢いと別れ上
从邂逅到分手
手に
我
打ち込んで
信手拈来
時間がくれば終わる Don't hurry!
时间到了结束掉就好 别着急！
愛に傷ついた
从感情受挫的那天起
あの日からずっと
就一直持续着
昼と夜が逆の
昼夜颠倒的生活
暮らしを続けて
一直持续着
はやりのDiscoで
好想赶快投身于流行的disco里忘情舞蹈
踊り明かすうちに
我就只学到了
おぼえた魔術
这些把戏
なのよ I'm sorry!
对不起啦
私のことを
绝对不要
決して本気で愛さ
认真地爱我
ないで 恋なんてただの
恋爱什么的只是游戏
ゲー ム 楽しめば
玩得尽兴就好
それでいいの
尽兴就好
閉ざした心を飾る
掩盖我封闭心灵的
派手なドレスも靴も
华丽礼服和鞋子
孤独な友だち
都是我孤独的朋友
私を誘う
令人讽刺的是
人は皮肉なものね いつも
邀请我的人 个个都像他一样
彼に似てるわなぜか
可是不知为何
思い出と
思绪和过去的记忆
重なり合う
重叠
グラスを落として急に
别问我
涙ぐんでも わけは
突然掉落在酒杯里的眼泪是
尋ねないでね
为了什么
夜更けの高速で
倒在深夜的高速边
眠りにつくころ
昏昏欲睡之时
ハロゲンライトだけ
只有路灯
妖しく輝く
闪耀着神秘的光
氷のように
像冰一样冷的女子
冷たい女だと
ささやく声がしても
在小声的说着
Don't worry
不用担心
I'm just playing games
我只是游戏人间
I know that's plastic love
我知道那是虚假的爱情
dance to the plastic beat
脆弱的心跳伴着我舞动迎来下一个黎明
another morning come
on just playing games
只是玩游戏
I know that's plastic love
我只是游戏人间 我知道那是虚假的爱情
Dance to the plastic beat
脆弱的心跳伴着我舞动
Another morning comes
迎来下一个黎明
I'm just
playing games I know that's plastic love
我只是在玩游戏 我知道那是塑料的爱
Dance to the plastic beat
随着塑料节拍起舞 又一个早晨来临
another morning comes
I'm just playing games
我只是游戏人间
I know that's plastic love
我知道那是虚假的爱情
dance to plastic beat another morning
脆弱的心跳伴着我舞动迎来下一个黎明
Comes oh,
来了哦
oh pog.
哦，nice。
Pog. OK
好的
I love that song so much.
我非常喜欢那首歌。
I love it so much yeah
我非常喜欢它是的
I'm just.
我只是。
~dude
〜伙计
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Plastic love will forever
be like top tier,
塑料爱情永远是顶级的，
top tier song
顶级歌曲，伙计。
all ever listen to your answer sing, man.
And they stay with me.
他们和我在一起。
They're just so fucking good.
他们真是太好了。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I forgot to ah to ask.
我忘了啊问。
Because I'm a
因为我是一个
Dumb arse. ah the volume sounds
笨蛋。 啊音量响
OK, cause I forgot to ask that.
好的，因为我忘了问这个。
After the first song.
在第一首歌之后。
Does it need any adjusting?
它需要任何调整吗？
I too quiet am I too loud?
我太安静了是不是太吵了？
Do I sound OK? Sounds sounds fine.
我听起来好吗？ 听起来不错。
I think. Sounds fine.
我认为。 听起来不错。
It's perfect.
这十分完美。
OK, nice. Thank you.
好的，不错。 谢谢你。
I don't really change it too much, but,
you know,
我并没有真正改变太多，但是，你知道，
I just want to make sure
it wasn't like too loud or too quiet.
我只是想确保它不会太响或太安静。
I don't want to, like, overpower the
the music
我不想，像，压倒音乐
I don't want to like
我不想喜欢
Sounds too quiet, either.
听起来也太安静了。
So, yeah, that one was plastic love.
所以，是的，那是塑料爱情。
I do the, I do the.
我做的，我做的。
Song a lot on the stream just because
it's, you know, it's a comfort song.
很多人在流媒体上唱歌只是因为它，你知道，这是一首安慰歌曲。
It's something that I'm.
这是我的东西。
It's like
when you go to McDonald's. Right?
就像你去麦当劳一样。 对？
And you get like the ten piece chicken
nuggets or like maybe you get the fries.
你会得到十块鸡块，或者你可能会得到薯条。
It's like the equivalent for me.
这对我来说是一样的。
It's like my, my nuggets and fries,
就像我的，我的鸡块和薯条，
essentially
本质上
so that's all I like.
所以这就是我喜欢的。
That's all I get
doing it a lot for everybody.
这就是我为每个人所做的一切。
Yeah, I do.
是的。
Payphone? Payphone.
payphone？payphone
I think that might be
a little too high for me.
我认为这对我来说可能有点太高了。
I've I'm not a pay phone.
我有我不是，payphone。
Yeah, no, no.
是的，不，不。
I don't think I can do it today.
我认为我今天做不到。
It's, like, really, really high.
它，就像，真的，真的很高。
A lot of songs that I have prepared
don't go to too much.
我准备的很多歌曲都没有太多。
And also, Maroon Five
而且，魔力红的音域也很疯狂，兄弟。
just has insane range, bro.
My God.
我的上帝。
One of these days I'll.
这些天我会的。
Be able
to, you know, increase my range that far.
能够，你知道，将我的范围扩大到那么远。
Something that I really.
东西，我真的。
Wish I could do
希望我能做到
is like.
就好像。
I really wish I could share.
我真的希望我能分享。
Recordings of when I used to sing back,
like, in back then,
我以前唱歌时的录音，比如，在那个时候，因为我以前经常练习，你知道，
because I used to practise a lot in the,
you know,
just record my shitty ...,
只是记录我的狗屎...，
you know, practise sessions
when I was a lot younger.
你知道，在我年轻的时候练习。
So I wish I could, like,
do a comparison before
所以我希望我可以之前做一个比较
and like with now
just to see how much I've grown
和现在一样，只是为了看看我成长了多少，因为有太多我无法喜欢的歌曲，
because there's like so many songs
that I wasn't able to like reach the,
the right range and stuff, but I'm just
oh no.
正确的范围和东西，但我只是哦，不。
I'm proud that we are able to
我很自豪我们能够
light switch Japanese version.
light switch日文版。
Oh my God, wait,
I've been addicted to that.
哦，我的上帝，等等，我已经上瘾了。
to that song recently, but I don't think I
最近听那首歌，但我不认为我
how does it how does it go again?
它是怎么回事它又是怎么回事？
Those are
那些是
mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
How did it go again?
又是怎么过的？
真夜中の「もしもし」どいう意味？わかんない
それでも電話を取った　yeah
いつも
恋人ふりをして
恋遊び
が好きだけ
That's a.
这是一个。
It's a really nice song.
这是一首非常好听的歌。
Oh, maybe next time. Fuck.
哦，也许下次吧。 他妈的。
That's a really good one.
这是一个非常好的。
Good suggestion, but I don't think I can
you know, do today,
好建议，但我想我不知道，今天做，
because it's, you know, Japanese lyrics
take some time to learn
因为它，你知道，日语歌词需要一些时间来学习
君に
魅力
された 今回が最後
だって　何度も 言ったのに
I think that's how it goes, right?
我想就是这样，对吧？
And then that's all I.
然后这就是我的全部。
Know because that's like,
知道，因为那就像，
you know, the parts I hear the most
on like tik-tok and shit
你知道，我听到最多的部分，比如 tik-tok
OK. Oh, for the for the next song. Mm.
好的。 哦，为了下一首歌。。
I don't know which I do or which I do.
我不知道我做什么或我做什么。
I'm like looking at my list right now. Uh,
我现在喜欢看我的清单。 呃，
you know,
你知道，
I might try.
我可能会尝试。
This out.
这出来了。
Because. Ah.
因为。 啊。
Yeah, I'll try this out.
是的，我会试试这个。
It's, um.
是，嗯。
It's an English song.
这是一首英文歌曲。
Yeah, this one is an English song.
是的，这是一首英文歌。
and.
和。
I. I thought about it a lot.
一、我想了很多。
Because I have a lot of,
you know, people in China that call me.
因为我在中国有很多人叫我。
Like, they call me Baobei and people say
that Baobei means treasure, right?
就像，他们叫我宝贝，人们都说宝贝是宝物的意思，对吧？
Or something precious. I don't know.
或者什么珍贵的东西。 我不知道。
So that got me thinking.
所以这让我思考。
I feel like I want to sing
我觉得我想唱一些与此相关的东西。
something related to that.
And what do you know?
你知道什么？
There's a song called Treasure.
有一首歌叫《宝藏》。
By Bruno Mars that I coincidentally.
巧合的是，布鲁诺·马尔斯（Bruno Mars）。
Also forgot. I knew how to sing. So
也忘记了。 我知道怎么唱歌。 所以
I'm going to do that
我要这样做，让我们来唱宝藏。
let's do treasure.
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, baby.
是的，宝贝。
That is what you want honey.
这就是你想要的。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
honey here. Let me treasure you.
亲爱的， 让我珍惜你。
OK, here it is.
好的，就是这样。
Uh, huh.
嗯。
OK. I think this is the right one.
好的。 我认为这是正确的。
Gimme, gimme, gimme attention, baby.
看过来,小宝贝，把你所有注意力放我身上
I got to tell you a little
something about yourself.
让我说点事吧
You're wonderful. Flawless. Who?
你真是完美的，无瑕的小女人
You sexy lady, too.
你性感的女人。
But you walk around here
like you wanna be someone else.
但你好像感觉不到我的存在
I know.
我知道你一直不清楚，没关系
Oh, I know that you don't know it,
but you're fine.
因为我马上就向所有人证明，你就是我的
So fine, fine, so fine.
宝贝，你这小宝贝
Oh, oh, oh, girl.
哦，哦，哦，女孩。
I'm gonna show you one.
因为我马上就向所有人证明
You're all mine, mine, mine. treasure.
你都是我的，我的，我的。 宝藏。
That is what you are.
那就是你。
honey.
宝贝
You're my golden star.
你是我天空中最亮的星。
You know you can make my wish come true
美梦成真的小星星
if you let me treasure you.
让我永远珍惜你
If you let me treasure you
珍惜你让我到永远
oh, oh, oh yeah.
小美女，小宝贝，朝我笑一笑
Pretty girl, pretty girl.
漂亮的姑娘，漂亮的姑娘。
You should be smiling
像你这么耀眼的女孩
A girl like you should never look so blue.
怎能如此忧伤
You're.
你是
everything I see in my dreams.
我连梦里都只有你
I wouldn't say that to you if it wasnt true
如果不是真的，我不会对你这么说
Oh, I know that you don't know it,
but you're fine,
如果这不是真的我不会这么说
so fine.
我知道你一直不清楚，没关系
Oh, oh, oh, oh, girl.
因为我马上就向所有人证明，你就是我的
I'm gonna show you when you're mine,
oh mine
宝贝，
treasure
你这小宝贝
that is what you are,
honey, you're my golden star.
亲爱的，你是我天空中最亮的星。
You know, you can make my wish come true
美梦成真的小星星
if you let me  treasure you.
让我永远珍惜你
Yeah, you
你是我的宝贝，我靓丽的宝贝
if you let me treasure
如果你让我珍惜
oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
You are my treasure You are my treasure.
你是我的宝贝 你是我的宝贝
You are my treasure yeah.
你是我的宝贝耶。
You, you, you, you you are
You are my treasure You are my treasure
你是我的宝贝 你是我的宝贝
you you, you treasure.
That is what you are,
这就是你，亲爱的。你是我天空中最亮的星。
honey.You're my golden star.
You know you can make my wish come true.
你知道你可以实现我的愿望。
If you let me treasure you.
如果你让我珍惜你。
If you let me treasure
如果你让我珍惜
oh, oh, yeah.
哦，哦，是的。
Ha ha, la.
哈哈，拉。
So, yeah,
I thought I was thinking of you guys when.
所以，是的，我以为我在想你们的时候。
I figured out, like, oh, treasure,
我想通了，就像，哦，treasure，
baby, that that's a
this would be a fun one.
treasure，那是一个，这将是一个有趣的。
to do.
歌曲。
Oh, fuck, yeah.
哦，他妈的，是的。
You're my treasure.
你是我的宝贝。
Let me get some more water.
让我再喝点水。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Clean your throat
like that is never a good idea.
那样清洁你的喉咙绝不是一个好主意。
I have such a bad habit of doing that
every time.
我有一个坏习惯，每次都这样做。
Don't do what I'm doing. Like, don't do.
不要做我正在做的事。
Like that.
像那样。
It's not healthy.
它不健康。
It's just, like. It's.
只是，就像。 它的。
Habitual.
习惯性的。
Like, once you start a habit of it,
it's really hard.
就像，一旦你开始养成它的习惯，它真的很难。
So it's really hard
to break the habit. You know,
所以真的很难改掉这个习惯。 你知道，
you guys enjoy that one.
你们喜欢那个。
Really? It's. Ah. I. I remember the song.
真的吗？ 它的。 啊。  I. 我记得这首歌。
Like, brings me back years ago
because, um.
就像，让我回到几年前，因为，嗯。
You know, I has a lot of.
你知道，我有很多。
A lot of good nostalgia
from, like, early on.
早期的很多美好的怀旧之情。
Tons of things, like 20, 12.
很多东西，比如20、12。
It's only 13 years it's ah.
这才13年啊。
It's a very.
这是一个非常。
You know, feel good but also just,
you know, Bruno Mars songs in general.
你知道，感觉很好，但也只是，你知道，布鲁诺马尔斯的歌曲一般。
It just has that fun vibe.
它只是有那种有趣的氛围。
Unless it's like a sad love song.
除非它像一首悲伤的情歌。
He does
他是这样的
yeah.
是的。
I haven't,
我没有，
I don't think I've sang it ever
and except for like years ago.
我想我从来没有唱过它，除了几年前。
So like doing this again,
所以喜欢再做一次，
it's just, man,
只是，伙计，
I don't know, it
just brought back that inner
我不知道，它只是带回了那个内在的
child, I guess.
童年，我猜。
Like,
像，
I'm just listening to the radio.
我只是在听收音机。
I'm singing in the backseat of the car
on a summer day.
夏日，我在汽车后座唱歌。
This is going to game driven to my
cousin's house or something like that.
这是要去我表弟家或类似的地方玩游戏。
I don't know.
That's what that's what gives me are
我不知道。 这就是给我的东西
memories of mostly OK.
回忆大多还行。
So I wanted to switch over
to a different place for this next song.
所以我想为下一首歌换个地方。
So give me a second.
所以给我一秒钟。
I'm going to change the
我要改变我们的位置。 是的。
our location. Yeah.
Good. Ginger location.
好的。
So be right back, really quickly.
All right. Mm hmm.
所以马上回来，真的很快。 好的。 嗯嗯。
Now just give me a second
现在给我一秒钟
I hope that wasn't sore.
我希望那还行。
You know, it's about
你知道，它是关于
everything looks good.
一切看起来都很好。
Yeah.
是的。
I want to come back here because I.
我想回到这里，因为我。
I think this would fit the vibes
better for the them
我认为这更适合他们的氛围
or the other songs
that I wanted to sing for you guys.
或者我想为你们唱的其他歌曲。
I, I do really love my fair
我，我真的很爱我的公会
share of K-pop or Korean songs.
分享 K-pop 或韩国歌曲。
And some.
还有一些。
Recently, I attempted to sing spring day.
最近，我试图唱春日。
I know you guys probably saw on Twitter,
我知道你们可能在 Twitter 上看到了，我确实在
and I did upload a
small version on YouTube, but
YouTube 上上传了一个小版本，但是
I wanted to learn the whole song,
想学整首歌
and that's exactly what I did.
这正是我所做的。
I learnt more except for the raw portions
because I'm not that good at rap yet.
除了原始部分，我学到了更多，因为我还不太擅长说唱。
I've learnt that I did
that the entirety of it or like
我知道我做了全部或喜欢
as much as I could of spring day
尽我所能的春日
and so I thought be a good idea
to share that with you
所以我觉得和你分享是个好主意
since it became one of my favourite songs.
因为它成了我最喜欢的歌曲之一。
While it is.
虽然它是。
Currently one of my favourite songs
because I learnt about it not too long ago
目前是我最喜欢的歌曲之一，因为我不久前才知道它，它只是，它是一种氛围，它是一种真正好的氛围，
and it's just been, it's been a vibe,
it's been a real good vibe and to,
you know, have it on my, have it on my playlist
你知道，在我的，在我的播放列表里
so that is our next song, Spring Day.
所以这是我们的下一首歌，春日。
It's really fitting too.
because you know why
它也很合适。 因为你知道为什么现在是春天和天气温暖的帮派。
it's currently Spring
and the gang in the warmer weather.
I'm getting my allergies.
我开始过敏了。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
I went out yesterday to go to the gym
我昨天出去去健身房，一出门我就打喷嚏，像湿透了一样。 但。
and as soon as I stepped outside
I was sneezing and like wet. But.
It just felt so gross
只是觉得太恶心了
because like, yeah, there's more.
因为喜欢，是的，还有更多。
The flowers are really blooming
now and are, you know, is warm.
花朵现在真的开花了，而且，你知道，很温暖。
And then I have appalonology though.
然后我有appalonology。
Yeah.
是的。
So I get a little I get the a stuffy nose,
所以我得到一点我得到一个鼻塞，
which is not the best when,
you know, you're trying to sing.
当你想唱歌的时候，这不是最好的。
So thank God it wasn't yesterday.
所以感谢上帝，这不是昨天。
OK? Oh, spring day
好的？ 哦，春日
lyrics.
歌词。
Romanised
罗马化，因为我无法读韩语（我也是啊痛苦）
because I cannot read on Google
OK, there you go.
好的，给你。
I really hope I don't butcher.
我真希望我不要唱毁。
I know one of my.
我知道我的一个。
Mods or like two of my mods are Korean
and I like to like had cannon in my head
模组或类似我的两个模组是韩语的，我喜欢在我的头上放大炮，有恶霸，每次我念错韩语时
that there are bullies
and every time I mispronounce a Korean
word they like,
they go Asian mom on me and they're like.
他们喜欢的话，他们对我来说是亚洲妈妈，他们就像。
Oh, how could you fuck this up?
哦，你怎么能搞砸这个？
You are terrible.
你太可怕了。
You got an f you
how could you do this to our family?
你拿f吧，你怎么能这样对我们的家人？
Disowned that or something. I don't know.
我不知道。
That's like I
这就像我
if I to if I like misspeak .
如果我喜欢说错话。
Like mis enunciate one
ah one honk or something it just them
就像发音错误一啊一按喇叭或只是他们
I'm going to hear the never hear
the end of it from a from a couple months.
几个月后，我将听到永远不会听到它的结束。
OK all right.
好的没问题。
Ah. So hope you guys enjoy
啊。 所以希望你们在下一个，春日，享受这个
this next one, spring day
and. Hopefully you pick.
希望你选择。
Some flowers sometime soon.
I really want to.
很快就会有一些花。 我真的很想。
Just go out and I don't know, I remember
只是出去，我不知道，我记得几年前在盖恩斯维尔去新加坡。
going to Singapore like a few years ago
in Gainesville.
I could go through the gardens
by the bay and start seeing the flowers.
我可以穿过海湾边的花园，开始看到鲜花。
There was really something
beautiful in God and I go back again.
上帝，真的有一些美好的东西，我又回去了。
There are so many flowers there.
那里有很多花。
It smelled so nice ha.
闻起来真香哈。
But OK,
但是没问题，
I'm ready.
我已经准备好了。
Dum dum dum bum bum.
嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟。
Bum bum bum bum.
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum.
허공을 떠도는 작은
就像飘在空中的
먼지처럼 작은
小小尘埃一般
먼지처럼
날리는 눈이 나라면
如果我是飘起的雪花的话
조금 더 빨리
是不是就可以快一点
네게 닿을 수 있을 텐데 눈꽃이 떨어져요
触碰到你 雪花飘落
또 조금씩 멀어져요
又渐渐远去
보고 싶다 보고 싶다
想你 念你
얼마나
还要等待多久
기다려야 또 몇 밤을 더 새워야
还要熬过多少个夜晚
널 보게 될까 널 보게 될까
才能够见你 才能够见你
만나게 될까
才能够见你
추운 겨울 끝을 지나
直到寒冬结束
다시 봄날이 올 때까지
春日来临之时
꽃 피울 때까지 그곳에 좀 더
直到花开之时 就在那里 再等等
머물러줘
再等等
Da da da da da da da
哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒
Da da da.
哒哒哒。
Da da da da
哒哒哒哒
시린 널
呼唤过冰冷的你
불어내 본다 연기처럼
就像烟雾一般
하얀 연기처럼
如同一缕青烟
말로는 지운다 해도 사실
就算嘴上说着要忘记你
난 아직 널 보내지 못하는데
其实我到现在也无法放开你
눈꽃이 떨어져요 또 조금씩
雪花飘落 又渐渐
멀어져요
远去
보고 싶다 보고 싶다
想你  念你
조금만
기다리면
只要
며칠 밤만 더
再等一会
새우면
只要再熬过几个夜晚
만나러 갈게
会去见你的
데리러 갈게
会带你走的
추운 겨울 끝을 지나
直到寒冬结束
다시 봄날이
春日
올 때까지
来临之时
꽃 피울 때까지
直到花开之时
그곳에 좀 더 머물러줘
就在那里 再等等
머물러줘
再等等
oh well.
好吧。
And that was spring day.
那是春日。
OK, I'm. Ready.
好的，我是。 准备好。
I'm ready for the I'm ready for the rubber
我准备好了，我准备好了橡胶人字拖会撞到我的屁股上。
flip flop to get, like,
smacked against my arse.
Because I know I fucked up.
因为我知道我搞砸了。
I'm ready.
我已经准备好了。
OK, who's going to who's going to do it.
OK，谁去谁来做。
Who's gonna
谁会
I don't know.
我不知道。
Who's the who's the.
Answer that's going to like.
会喜欢的回答。
You know, assault me cause I fucked up.
你知道，攻击我吧，因为我搞砸了。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'm just kidding.
我只是开玩笑。
Muh uh. Uh.
嗯嗯。 呃。
Yeah.
是的。
Thought I really enjoy the, um,
the melody for this song.
以为我真的很喜欢这首歌的旋律。
Is so beautiful.
是如此美丽。
The chorus, the pre-chorus.
合唱，预合唱。
Is so it's just so good.
是这样吗，太好了。
Like, God damn, man
就像，该死的，伙计
was it?
是吗？
I think it was I it's I'm cooking.
我想是我，
Was it Jin?
是金唱的部分吗？
I hope they're they're
parts are really good.
我希望他们是他们的部分真的很好。
I think I'm.
我想我是。
I'm just a big fan of ballads,
I think. Yeah.
我想，我只是民谣的忠实粉丝。 是的。
And a song that's just like a ballad
really, really hits for me.
一首就像民谣一样的歌，真的，真的很适合我。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Uh, thank you, guys.
嗯，谢谢各位。
It makes me feel better.
这让我感觉好多了。(下期见~）
I'm gonna do.
我会做的。
Another one from most likely.
另一个最有可能的。
I have a couple in mind.
我有几个想法。
I want to try a
我想再试一次。
again.
From last time.
从上次开始。
I've sang one of these before.
我以前唱过其中一首。
But I feel like
I could do a little better.
但我觉得我可以做得更好一点。
Yeah, I feel like I could do it
a little better than last time.
是的，我觉得我可以比上次做得更好一些。
I know.
我知道。
If you guys remember, you want wanna sing?
如果你们还记得，你们想唱歌吗？
Yes. You want to go? Yes.
是的。 你想去？ 是的。
I was
我曾是
it's another odds in her career and one
这是她职业生涯中的另一种可能性
song so deep comma.
歌好深的逗号。
No, it is not deep. Come
不，它不深。 来
no villon.
没有维隆。
Eh? You got it.
诶？ 你说对了。
Yeah.
是的。
Next one is gonna be Villon.
下一个将是维隆。
And filling is such a is such a bop.
填充物就是这样的。
I feel like I've listened to it
so many times.
我感觉我已经听了很多遍了。
But I never somehow get tired of it.
但我从不厌倦它。
It's just really fucking good.
这真是他妈的好。
Yeah.
是的。
One of these days,
I do want to learn a six on sunset deja vu
这些天中的一个，我确实想在日落似曾相识的时候学习一个六
all like like like
都喜欢喜欢
like you guys are like
the one that's like.
就像你们一样。
That says a who does love. You?
那就是说一个爱的人。 你？
I forgot the people that sing that down
我忘记了唱这首歌的人
I'm still trying to learn that
我仍在努力向你们学习，但很快
one from you guys, but soon
is not is an easy song.
不是一首容易的歌。
This is definitely not an easy song. So.
这绝对不是一首轻松的歌。 所以。
OK, well, all right.
好的，好的，好的。
Here we go, villain.
来了，恶棍。
Let's see if I still got it.
让我们看看我是否仍然得到它。
Oh, I'm doing drink some.
哦，我正在喝一些。
More water before we get into it.
在我们进入之前更多的水。
So I don't like overdo.
所以我不喜欢过分。
Anything.
任何事物。
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
流氓，流氓，流氓，流氓，流氓，流氓，流氓。
Like I want to do more.
就像我想做更多。
Yeah.
是的。
Slowly integrating more Korean songs
慢慢地将更多的韩国歌曲融入到我的曲目中
into my, like, repertoire
or like, I was I know how to sing
或者像，我是我会唱歌
Korean. OK,
韩国人。 好的，
we are
我们假装是好人的英雄。
pretend to be the heroes on the good side.
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Autumn Tonga's
song going on sec autumn goes on I on sick
Autumn Tonga 的歌在 sec
sick on your coffee
pick up on me on all the gay
继续秋天继续我生病生病了你的咖啡拿起我所有的同性恋
nunchuck inside of me go yeah not one
双节棍在我体内走，是的，不是我的一侧
side of me
Go Sammy on me Sad song Gun her back
Go Sammy on me 悲伤的歌 Gun her back
So many shades of grey
这么多灰色调
Oh get a not a song he saw
哦，得到一首他看过的歌曲
Oh Could easily
哦 可以轻松地说这是我在路上擅长的一种方式
say it's a way I'm good on the roads
Oh, it's him Not because I'm a villain
When I got to sing again
哦 是他 不是因为我是反派 当我又要唱歌的时候
It's not where my guns are going
Oh, my guts and mine got it
这不是我的枪的去向哦，我的胆量和我的得到它
Well yeah I fell learn
and I got to sing again
好吧，是的，我学会了，我又要唱歌了
Midsummer lights on omega on the on
and some shake on me
仲夏灯亮着欧米茄，有些摇晃着我
So I'm killing someone
Maybe killing someone
所以我在杀人 也许杀人
Maybe I'm killing you
who maybe are killing me Maybe we are.
也许我杀了你谁也许杀了我也许我们是。
Pretend to be the heroes on the good side
But what if we're the villains on the.
假装是好人的英雄，但如果我们是坏人呢。
Other
其他
am I good?
我好吗？
I'm a bad a are you good or bad?
我是坏人你是好人还是坏人？
A man gets a
一个男人没有度蜜月，没有枪，没有回来，然后枪手又说，我们好吗？
no honeymoon and gun and no return
and then a gunman again say, are we good?
Are we bad?
我们不好吗？
Eh, what is good or is bad?
呃，什么是好什么是坏？
A they get
他们一到那里度了蜜月，就拿着枪说，我比一个女孩烧得要死。
there were a honeymoon, a gun and said,
I'm burning than a girl just sick.
Say so many shades of grey.
说这么多灰色阴影。
Took out the mortar saw a saw Oh good.
拿出迫击炮锯一锯哦好。
Easily fades away I'm bored
很容易消失我无聊，根源太多，因为我爱。
and the roots are too much because I love.
And when they're cursing like a tomato
and more guns
当他们像西红柿一样诅咒和更多的枪
I'll come on
maggots and lying Go love you love
我会来蛆和撒谎去爱你爱
And I never got to sing God Good Matsumoto
da dum I'm a gun The un and some shit
And I never got to sing God Good
Matsumoto da dum I am a gun 联合国和一些狗屎
Chicago is soft
All villains When I go to sing
芝加哥很软所有的恶棍当我去唱歌时
I do not
我不戴更多的枪我会来
wear more guns I'll come
ohmygod roaring Go to LA
We're all villains And then I go to sing
God Give me some love Oh my God.
我们都是恶棍然后我去唱歌上帝给我一些爱哦我的上帝。
And oh dudes and blah.
哦，伙计们，等等。
I'm killing someone
maybe or killing someone
我可能正在杀死某人或正在杀死某人，也许我正在杀死可能正在杀死我的你。
and maybe I'm killing you
who maybe are killing me.
Maybe we are priests
and we're the heroes on the good side
也许我们是牧师，我们是好人的英雄
but what if we're the villains
on the other?
但如果我们是对方的反派呢？
We all pretend to be the heroes
on the good side.
我们都假装是好人的英雄。
But what if we're the villains
on the other.
但是，如果我们是对方的恶棍怎么办。
We are pretend to be the heroes on
我们假装是好人的英雄。
the good side.
Are I try to go
我是否尝试像一个很酷的变焦镜头一样在阁楼里，我想我有。
for like a cool zooms are in the loft
I think I I've.
Fucked up on the back. Down.
背上完蛋了 向下。
Got is a hard as.
得到是一个艰难的作为。
Far as hard how does it
怎么这么难
oh the good easily fades away part. Ooh.
哦，好的很容易消失的部分。 哦。
Yeah it's like trying to do a zone change
there is rough
是的，这就像尝试进行区域更改一样粗糙，但是或者像音高更改一样，边缘粗糙
but or like a pitch change
there is rough edges
I feel like a
I feel like we did a good job
我觉得我觉得我们做得很好
I feel like I see a job
我觉得我看到了一份工作
I love the raw
I think if there's a favourite
我喜欢生的我想如果有最喜欢的
part of that song for me it's
definitely the
这首歌的一部分对我来说绝对是
it's definitely the middle rap.
绝对是中游。
I love it so much.
我非常喜欢。
It just like it goes, it
just you're such a.
它就像它一样，它只是你这样一个。
Good that you could flow so it so it's
not too long, it's not too noisy or short.
很好，你可以流动，所以它不会太长，也不会太吵或太短。
It just works.
它只是工作。
They get to day on a. Hunt
and the guns that have been in.
他们到了一天。 亨特和已经进入的枪支。
The gods are sick, sad,
众神生病，悲伤，
it's really a
它真的是一个
it's addictive.
它很容易上瘾。
I think that's the word I'm looking for.
我想这就是我要找的词。
Addictive. It's a deal.
上瘾。 这是一笔交易。
Also. Thank you for the hype train, guys.
还。 谢谢你们的炒作火车，伙计们。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
I really appreciate all the
the support we're getting tonight.
我真的很感谢我们今晚得到的所有支持。
And like I said before,
I promise I'll read through everything
就像我之前说的，我保证我会在卡拉
at the end of the karaoke session. OK.
OK 结束时通读所有内容。 好的。
I'll do my best.
我会尽力而为。
Congrats on three energy. Kay.
恭喜三能。 凯。
Thank you, guys.
谢谢你们。
You're part of that.
你是其中的一部分。
300 k is like, yo, we were here.
300 k 就像，哟，我们在这里。
You know, we were. Here.
你知道，我们是。 这里。
As me bang my chest.
当我敲打我的胸膛时。
It's not a good idea.
这不是一个好主意。
That kind of hurt. Oof!
那种伤。 钱币！
I just it was all
我只是这一切
it was a monkey.
那是一只猴子。
Woo monkey
呜猴
been influenced by too many other beats.
受到太多其他节拍的影响。
Ubers.
优步。
I am like slowly adapting their language
and behavioural rhythms into my own
我喜欢慢慢地将他们的语言和行为节奏适应我自己的节奏
it's, it's.
是的，是的。
It's not like it's not bad thing,
that thing.
并不是说它不是坏事，那件事。
Yeah.
是的。
So it's kind of like endearing,
you know. OK.
所以这有点像可爱，你知道的。 好的。
So, all right, this saw this next song
所以，好吧，这看到了下一首歌
I wanted to sing
我想唱歌
this next song
is one that I learnt recently
下一首歌是我最近学的
and it was at the request
of another guilty.
这是应另一个有罪的人的要求。
Maybe they're in the chat right now.
也许他们现在正在聊天中。
I'm, I'm not sure but I, I learnt the song
because I remember
我，我不确定，但我，我学这首歌是因为我记得
promising I could try and I did and.
承诺我可以尝试，我做到了。
It's like
它像是
I'm. I'm baffled
我是。 我对我们已经走到这一步感到困惑。
guys that we've come this far.
I know I've said it many times
and it feels like I'm being a dead horse.
我知道我已经说过很多次了，感觉就像我是一匹死马。
At this point, but I really just cannot
在这一点上，但我真的不能
fathom everything you all have given me.
了解你们给我的一切。
And many times I've touted my decisions
很多次我吹捧我的决定
I've doubted my self-worth,
I doubt in my efforts.
我怀疑自己的价值，怀疑自己的努力。
But every time I have those thoughts
但每次我有这些想法
that seem to cloud my judgement
这似乎使我的判断蒙上阴影
it's.
它的。
It's always you.
永远是你。
All that helped pull me from it
and make me realise
所有这些都帮助我摆脱了困境，让我意识到你们都在这里。
that you're all very much here.
You're, you're all
你是，你们都是我所拥有的最善良和最支持的灵魂
some of the kindest
and most supportive souls I've had
the honour to call my guild members,
and it really hasn't been easy since.
有幸召集我的公会成员，从那以后真的不容易。
Sometimes I do feel like
有时我确实觉得
I'm on my own
as an independent streamer, but.
我是一个独立的主播，但是。
It's like an art.
这就像一门艺术。
It's an obstacle
I'm learning to surmount every day.
这是我每天都在学习克服的障碍。
And I. Have.
我有。
Good friends, I have like really good
friends that convince me otherwise.
好朋友，我有很多非常好的朋友，他们让我信服。
And it's because of you guys
and it's because of my dear friends
这是因为你们，也是因为我亲爱的朋友们
that I'm reminded of that
我想起了那个
I'm reminded of that fervent love.
我想起了那份炽热的爱。
And I owe you the world's
我欠你全世界的
I owe you guys the world for making me
live what feels like a dream.
我欠你们这个世界，让我活得像梦一样。
And for
在我能记住的最长的时间里，我一直想
the longest I could remember,
I've always wanted to
make people happy while enjoying things.
让人们在享受事物的同时快乐。
Something I, I love to do.
我喜欢做的事。
And this felt perfect.
这感觉很完美。
And it felt more than right. And
而且感觉非常正确。 而这一切都是因为你
it's all because of you
and your support
that I could be here right now.
以及您对我现在可以在这里的支持。
Streaming every day as often as I do
in the mornings.
每天都像我早上一样经常流式传输。
And. In the nights
to give everyone a chance to see me live.
和。 在晚上让每个人都有机会看到我的生活。
And it understand
它了解我对你们的看法
how much I think about you guys like
and how much I love you all for helping me
be who I am.
以及我多么爱你们所有人帮助我成为我自己。
Like despite all the milestones.
就像所有的里程碑一样。
And we just keep continuing
to grow bigger and bigger by the day.
而且我们只是继续不断地变得越来越大。
And I just.
而我只是。
I see how much love you all
put into the community,
我看到你们对社区投入了多少爱，
all the fan arts,
all the all the support of comments.
所有的粉丝艺术，所有的评论支持。
Every time you show up, every time you're
here, every time you come in, it's simply
每次你出现，每次你在这里，每次你进来，简直就是
it's just
it's amazing.
太棒了。
And I really I really.
我真的我真的。
Couldn't smile harder at the thought
一想到每天都能看到这一幕，我就笑不出来了。
of being blessed to see this every day.
And I never want to let that go.
我永远不想放手。
I really I
I don't want to let it go, ever.
我真的我不想让它过去，永远。
And one day I hope that
我希望有一天
I can learn to see myself
我可以学着看自己，也许你们都看我，
as you all see me maybe,
and know why you continue to support
知道你为什么继续支持这个经常尖叫的愚蠢男孩。
this dumb boy who screams a lot so much.
And is what, Suzie?
是什么，苏西？
24, seven.
24，七。
One day I'll know, but I'm getting there.
有一天我会知道，但我会到达那里。
I promise.
我保证。
This next song is called Dry Flower,
下一首歌叫Dry Flower，希望大家喜欢。
and I hope you guys enjoy it.
Double with us.
和我们加倍。
Sit on the cooter in the yo yo knife with.
坐在 yo yo 刀上的 cooter 上。
Re that the sea geyser looking back
and go back to see this
Re that the sea geyser
回首过去，回头看看这个
gold man there Sudan.
金人有苏丹。
I saw the the DA he thought the start
我看到了
zero and nine there without accuracy gain
I hate the song and not the buck hurry
DA，他认为从零开始到九点没有准确度增益我讨厌这首歌，而不是急于求成
and thus they die on their mercy he took
因此他们死于他的怜悯
oh gaga there I had to kill no cop.
哦，嘎嘎，我不得不杀死任何警察。
Oh, well, what are their guru
gonna do you?
哦，好吧，他们的大师会怎么做？
Not some.
不是一些。
Oh, I'll listen, you cat it's
哦，我会听的，你这猫
never gone.
从未离开。
Them up on the cool Nova.
他们在凉爽的新星上。
Yeah, come on.
是啊来吧。
Come on, Bucky.
来吧，巴基。
You not talk of Sandbu.
你不说桑德布。
Send the camera.
送相机。
He's on the line.
他上线了。
All good eye food.
所有好的眼睛食物。
I've meet the key needle
in my living room.
我在客厅碰到了钥匙针。
Keep going.
继续前进。
Keep the key.
保留钥匙。
Thaw can't eat us
解冻不能吃我们
starving.
挨饿。
He needs another good day.
他需要另一个美好的一天。
OK, Arthur Monoxide.
好的，亚瑟一氧化。
It had gotten. Warm.
I see what that's about.
它得到了。 温暖的。 我明白那是关于什么的。
Guarding their GitHub memo.
保护他们的 GitHub 备忘录。
Knock not
不敲门
Anthony gonna see you got it.
安东尼会看到你得到它。
And the gun got out the bubble suit
at the gun
枪从枪口脱出泡泡服
authority he thought I'm not became you a.
权威他以为我没有变成你了。
Sound like accurate that you look a lot.
听起来很准确，你看起来很多。
More calm oh no the can he got us
更冷静哦，不，他能得到我们吗
I need I need
我需要我需要
sea pick on me that whole sea
整片海都在我身上
so good guy
he no Kiawah then been done there
好家伙，他没有 Kiawah 然后在那里完成
then you see the kids in the
in the tar scar
然后你看到焦油疤痕中的孩子们看到汉字称他为一对夫妇更多的布吉
see hanzi
call him a couple more boogie on that
all come off Tyburn emo
全部从 Tyburn emo 中脱身
kid he turned nine off
孩子，他关掉了九点
goodbye food I wanna eat
再见食物我想吃鸭子到你的枪那里得到吧。
duck to your gun got that there bar.
Keep the keep the.
保持保持。
Key to keep the euro us around
保持欧元在我们身边的关键
Zaki I got
Zaki 我知道他需要我的妈妈，你准备好保留很多东西
he need my mom guy
you ready to keep the lot
the same model casita a two corral
you mean you see Kaci
同款 casita 两个畜栏
gaga boom
你的意思是你看到 Kaci gaga 热潮
a cocky
一个名叫虎鲸的自大眼睛霍根坐在枪上
eyed Hogan who named the orca
sit on the gun
no, ma'am, I will your boo Sookie
your game or team attack
不，女士，我会你的嘘声 Sookie
oh, come on,
你的比赛或团队攻击哦，来吧，
come on, Bucky Not the law Come on sand.
来吧，巴基 不是法律 来吧，沙滩上。
Sand.
沙。
He Kira he die of murder a in my eye
他基拉他死于谋杀我眼中的一个现在就在这个上。
now came in this on this.
Sit, sit, sit.
坐，坐，坐。
Does the car got your.
车有没有你的。
How ok
怎么样
oh. I.
哦。 一世。
A fun fact.
一个有趣的事实。
Sorry. Let me take a drink.
对不起。 让我喝一杯。
When.
什么时候。
I. I learnt this song
一、学了这首歌
literally today.
从字面上看今天。
I learnt it today and I, I know it's some.
我今天学到了，我知道它是一些。
No it's really beautiful.
不，它真的很漂亮。
I remember I lost.
我记得我输了。
Again, like I said before,
actually getting to sing the song
再一次，就像我之前说的，实际上要唱这首歌
and see the, you know, I
看看，你知道，我
let go of the flow and learn the flow
and like realise how.
放开心流，学习心流，就像意识到如何去做。
It's just it's such.
就是这样。
A different experience and
不一样的体验和
I'm really happy
that you guys recommended this to me.
我真的很高兴你们向我推荐了这个。
It's a really amazing song
and I like it a lot.
这是一首非常棒的歌，我非常喜欢。
It's probably going to be
它可能会是
something I sing again in in the future.
我以后再唱的东西。
For Iraqi refugees to come.
伊拉克难民的到来。
They must feel like I like.
他们一定觉得我喜欢。
The kid, the.
那个孩子，那个。
Kid, the kid, the kid to eat asks. For.
孩子，孩子，吃饭的孩子问。 为了。
It feels nice and all.
感觉很好。
All my friends really like the song Sil.
我所有的朋友都非常喜欢这首歌 Sil。
Oh God.
天啊。
So thank you to the guilty
I don't know who you were, but
所以感谢有罪的我不知道你是谁，但是
I remember your recommendation
and saw it is
我记得你的推荐，看到它是
is by all means very well
appreciated that you know,
非常感谢您知道，您让我写下来并尝试参加本次会议。
you got me to write it down
and try for this session.
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
I feel like I want to.
我觉得我想要。
Do it again, though.
不过，再做一次。
Mm. Would you guys.
毫米。 你们会吗。
You guys be.
你们是。
OK with me trying it one more time?
可以让我再试一次吗？
Encore! Yeah.
再来一次！ 是的。
Encore! Encore!
再来一次！ 再来一次！
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I forgot to put it in the list. Ah.
我忘了把它放在清单上。 啊。
All I see.
我所见。
Dry flower
干花
Now let's do it one more time.
现在让我们再做一次。
Hmm. OK.
唔。 好的。
I, ah.
我，啊。
You know, I feel like I could.
你知道，我觉得我可以。
I could do better.
我可以做得更好。
I can do better.
我能做得更好。
This one.
这个。
This one, for sure.
这个，肯定的。
Hmm. Thank you.
唔。 谢谢你。
My guy.
我的家伙。
The balloon
气球与我们 Zeitoun 的任何你所有你的好。
with us Zeitoun the good
the any you all you.
Life with daddy dog
Percy keys who came back in.
与回来的狗爸爸珀西钥匙一起生活。
The back to see the sun go man
背着看太阳去的人他说唐娜通过雕像寻求主达基思
he said Donna sought the Lord
the DA Keith though the statue
when lying there with three kids
he came yeah.
当他和三个孩子躺在那里时，他来了，是的。
The saw on that the bakery and asked
if they on their.
看到面包店，问他们是否在他们的。
Most seats gonna go Google their there
大多数座位会去谷歌他们那里
I out y'all know a cop
我出去你们都知道警察哦，埃里克加纳能做什么
oh what out there could Eric Garner
are you what son of Amazon
你是亚马逊的儿子吗
he carried along on the bird gone then
他带着那只鸟走了
told me now oh yeah come on
现在告诉我哦，是的，来吧
come on the kill not saw
来吧 杀 没 看见 来 圣诞老人 沙子
come on Santa sand
Kira he turned I know Dora
基拉他转身我认识朵拉
he thought of me die
Kaemi the law he be more
他想我死了 Kaemi 的法律他更
keep the key to keep the key
保留钥匙 保留钥匙 我所说的一切
to it all I said
the balloon
气球
Kimmy to knock they your God
the whole narcos said it
Kimmy to knock them your
it got blown
I see what does see but God isn't
God 整个毒贩都说它被炸毁了
there could all be more knock
not Anthony can now see you about got it
可能会有更多的敲门声，安东尼现在看不到你了，枪越多越适合我们
the more the gun got out there
above us suited
the gun authority thought on that boogie
You are.
枪支权威认为你是那个布吉。
The lucky Jared.
幸运的杰瑞德。
That you do look and Mark
Oh no beat Acuna He got a
你确实看起来和马克哦，没有击败阿库纳他得到了一些高需要任何运气
some high need any luck
see taconite a ha see so go green
看到铁燧石，哈哈，所以去绿色
coloured then I mean the
有色然后我的意思是羽绒必须看到谷氨酰胺
the down must see that glutamine
mean that scar see he call him on
意思是那个伤疤看到他叫他
come on the will you not.
来吧，你不会。
Oh come on kaboom e
哦，来吧，kaboom e mom
mom all Chiara he done I all
all Chiara he done I all
but I food of a meat duck
但我吃肉鸭
you gun
go about there bar keep the keep the
你枪去那里吧保持保持保持
kids are key to he Ramos at
孩子是拉莫斯的关键
uh psyche
嗯，一个警卫，他需要我妈妈奥尔加
a guard he need my mom Olga
you read to get thought
the same old dog Garciaparra Good
I mean this easily
同一条老狗 Garciaparra 好，我的意思是这很容易走开
go kaboom
a cocky I you don't go moon they now
一个自大的我你不去月球他们现在都很酷
all cool suit Don that the my mommy
well your boo zuccato e your game
or team locker oh come on
或者团队更衣室哦，来吧
come on brother Keon that's all
来吧，科恩兄弟，一切都来吧！
come on send send
he kid I need
我需要他的孩子
I Your mother got in my eye now
well came in he's
我现在你妈妈已经进入我的眼里了
all at this sit, sit, sit,
sit the cock at your.
坐在你的公鸡。
House
房子
how are.
怎样。
And that was a dry flour
那是干面粉
strive la mm
努力啦mm
I hope you guys enjoyed that
我希望你们喜欢
I think I thank you for the anchor.
我想我感谢你的主播。
No problem.
没问题。
I think, you know,
我想，你知道，
I feel like if I didn't do it justice,
usually I want to like, redo write
我觉得如果我没有做到公正，通常我想喜欢，重做
this onto every deal.
这适用于每笔交易。
If I feel like,
you know, I could have done better at it.
如果我觉得，你知道，我本可以做得更好。
Oh, thank you so much, guys. Oh.
哦，非常感谢你们，伙计们。 哦。
You're also nice, all of you.
你们也很好，你们。
Are you too nice to me?
你对我太好了吗？
I wasn't that.
我不是那样的。
Great.
伟大的。
I'm still I'm.
我还是我。
Still trying to get used to the song.
还在努力适应这首歌。
Eventually, I'll get better.
最终，我会变得更好。
I mean, do you like it better? Right
我的意思是，你更喜欢它吗？ 对了，非常感谢您的聆听。
thank you so much listening.
And thank you for being nice
谢谢你的好
about
关于
about every every song I've done so far.
到目前为止我所做的每一首歌。
I really like all of you guys heard the
我真的很喜欢你们所有人听到这首歌的第一个版本。
the first take version
of this song before it's.
But it is really fucking good, man.
但这真的很好，伙计。
Yuri is his voice is amazing.
尤里是他的声音是惊人的。
So, I mean,
I could not hold a candle to his voice
所以，我的意思是，我无法接受他的声音
compared to mine, like, in terms of like,
is a I like his ability to sing the song.
比起我的喜欢，就喜欢而言，是一首我喜欢他的歌的能力。
I mean, he wrote the song.
我的意思是，他写了这首歌。
So but then one of these days,
I'm gonna get better at the song.
所以，但在这些日子里，我会在这首歌上做得更好。
Your first take is amazing.
你的第一个镜头太棒了。
All over a lot of the people they bring on
and the songs that they tell
他们带来的很多人以及他们讲述的歌曲
the one of my favourites of all time
was the.
我最喜欢的之一是。
It's got none, none of her dah dah done.
什么都没有，她的咩咩都没有完成。
I'm on the.
我在。
Whatever that song was God of.
不管那首歌是上帝的。
I known them on my.
我认识他们。
Yeah, I think
是的，我认为
like the first day for
that was really cute and fun.
就像第一天那样真的很可爱很有趣。
Mm. OK.
毫米。 好的。
Oh, I mean, it's a stretch.
哦，我的意思是，这是一个延伸。
It's, I need to stretch my back
是的，我需要伸展我的背部
and my neck
还有我的脖子
so it doesn't get stuff like I feel.
所以它不会得到我感觉的东西。
Like I tense. Up my entire upper body.
像我一样紧张。 我的整个上半身。
When I sing,
so I need to stretch like everything. Out
当我唱歌时，我需要像所有东西一样伸展。
so it doesn't get, like, all knotted up.
出来，所以它不会得到，就像，都打结了。
All right, that's bad for me.
好吧，这对我不利。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
I sing.
我唱歌。
Nicole. Nicole, I dash.
妮可。 妮可，我冲。
You mean Nicole by this?
你是说妮可吗？
All My God, that's
that's another hard one.
天哪，那是另一个困难的问题。
You know, I'll add that to the list.
你知道，我会把它添加到列表中。
Maybe we can try and learn it someday.
也许有一天我们可以尝试学习它。
And what's a really good song?
什么是真正好歌？
I look it up
我查一下
because I remember listening to that.
因为我记得听过那个。
A lot's
很多
oh, here it is.
哦，在这里。
Oh, no, that's not it.
哦，不，不是这样的。
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
No, I can't find it.
不，我找不到。
Ah, Vine.
啊，藤。
Oh, it's. Song you're talking about.
哦，是的。 你说的歌。
His voice is magical till
他的声音很神奇，这首歌真的很好
and the song is just really good
in my circulation.
在我的流通中。
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。 嗯嗯。
That's on Monza ora
那是在蒙扎奥拉
OK. Are
好的。 是
I want to try something.
我想尝试一些东西。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
I want to try.
我想尝试。
Something a little different.
有点不同的东西。
I, I was considering not doing this. One
我，我正在考虑不这样做。 一
and, like, not including it, but I feel.
而且，就像，不包括它，但我觉得。
Like.
像。
It shouldn't be too bad.
应该不会太糟糕。
I. Hmm.
一、嗯。
Bear with me.
忍受我。
I kind of want to give it a shot.
我有点想试一试。
All right. Yeah, I'll give it a shot.
好的。 是的，我会试一试。
I'll write it down on the plus, I think.
我想我会把它写在加号上。
I don't know if you guys know this one,
but I know it's known by a different name,
我不知道你们是否知道这个，但我知道它有一个不同的名字，但这就像，大多数人都知道的那个
but this is, like,
the one that most people know it by
it's a very short song
这是一首非常短的歌曲，直到 OK。
until OK.
I see.
我懂了。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Oh, my.
天啊。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Lyrics.
歌词。
I'm not.
我不是。
I did that.
我这样做了。
The mother died, and then.
母亲死了，然后。
OK, and now you're not gonna
好的，现在你不会听到了。
hear it.
Is OK.
可以。
So meet diagnostic.
所以满足诊断。
Don't die then, huh?
那就不要死了吧？
All right,
好的，
so my the commode,
they're don't don't the die.
所以我的马桶，他们是不做不死的。
Go, Mom.
去吧，妈妈。
You mean the look,
not the to go knock may.
您的意思是外观，而不是敲门声。
Well, I could die and only but the Galina.
好吧，我可能会死，但只有加林娜。
Yeah.
是的。
Get them on that gas on me see.
让他们在我身上加油，看看。
On their game then my also go
在他们的比赛中我也去移动你所有的上帝都是如此。
move the lot you all the God it's so.
I that come out that don't want to die.
出来的我不想死。
I don't know I mean I'm not going to go
look in the mirror Black Dynamite
我不知道我的意思是我不会去照镜子 Black Dynamite
Mama bear.
熊妈妈。
Go find them. Yeah.
去找他们。 是的。
Get them on the
gas on me see like I'm. The
让他们在我身上加油，就像我一样。 这
sick and want the not the Yoba.
生病了，想要的不是尤巴。
Garza died in my midline.
加尔萨死在我的中线。
Look the burn on the head they are
看看他们头上的烧伤
there I see no harm done.
我认为没有造成任何伤害。
Look him let's see it doc madame
看看他让我们看看医生夫人
a doc or dom or that they used this song
or God
一个医生或医生，或者他们在他们的盐上再次使用这首歌或上帝那长长的空手道东西，盐，全部。
that long karate thing on again
on their salt, the salt, the all.
See them with that.
看到他们。
I see Sagi now khaki
well I see bands and that go ducks in it
我看到 Sagi 现在卡其色很好我看到乐队和那去鸭子
He wanted that sword the awesome like this
他想要那把剑就这么厉害。 曾是
that. Was
I might.
我可能。
Know.
知道。
A Miri do that
美里这样做
encore encore
安可 安可
Mike one more time our time.
迈克再来一次我们的时间。
But I'm. Done
但是我。 完毕
yeah one more time
是的，再来一次
it once more once. More.
它再一次。 更多的。
This is such a stupid
I don't know why this.
这是多么愚蠢，我不知道这是为什么。
Came into my head.
进入我的脑海。
The Jonesy on fire.
琼西着火了。
I just really wanted to give it a shot.
我只是真的想试一试。
I said, fuck it.
我说，去他妈的。
Right?
对？
Fucking
他妈的
behind the.
在...后面。
It's my command.
这是我的命令。
They're gone.
他们走了。
Don died.
唐死了。
The low can mean they're not going to go.
低可能意味着他们不会去。
I'm not gonna be well.
我不会好起来的。
I could die in the near not go find you.
我可能死在附近找不到你。
Yeah, get them on the Carson.
是的，让他们上卡森。
You see, I'm their guy.
你看，我是他们的人。
I'm not the
我不是病得最厉害的月份，玛莎全是上帝。
most sick month, the Martha all but God.
It's only like a small deck. Don't.
它只是一个小甲板。 不。
Don't die, though, Mama.
不过，不要死，妈妈。
Do you mean they're not gonna to go?
你的意思是他们不会去？
I'm not gonna live or die, Mommy.
我不会生也不会死，妈妈。
Not going die.
不会死。
Yeah. Get in the gas on me.
是的。 给我加油。
See, on that guy.
看，在那个人身上。
My dad mos again.
我爸妈又来了。
Not the Lord, the father.
不是主，是父亲。
But that and Medina.
但那和麦地那。
But the burn dead
and that they all died there.
但烧死了，他们都死在那里。
I seen the home, the marquee Nazi doc
我看到了这个家，那个该死的纳粹医生和夫人。
and Madama that God damn that.
They used this song God Dead or La.
他们用这首歌God Dead or La。
Guardia dying on the.
瓜迪亚奄奄一息。
Get on this song.
上这首歌。
The sort the all see, the.
所有人都看到的那种。
My God, I see the guy in the khaki.
天哪，我看到那个穿卡其色的人了。
No, I see the that cynic
what he met the guy
不，我看到那个愤世嫉俗的人，他遇到了那个人
and then that saw
the Austin light this that.
然后看到奥斯汀点亮了这个那个。
It's not it's not a very.
它不是它不是一个非常。
Long song so.
长歌如此。
I've them them Donald but out the down
我有他们他们唐纳德但出局
but out I'm.
但我出来了。
Yeah.
是的。
This one's a Vega is a bill mean
by love it a. Lot.
爱它一个。 很多。
Because it's a little silly
因为有点傻
can on my one
可以在我的一个上再在我的一个上什么在里面就是那个就是那个。
more on my one what's in there
that's the that's the.
Song I mean I think
it's like I forgot the. Original song.
歌我的意思是我想它就像我忘记了一样。 原曲。
It is not.
它不是。
Actually called that it's like there's a
实际上叫它就像有一个它来自其他东西我只是忘记了名字。
it's from something else
I just forgot the name.
It's like an OSD from a game I believe.
它就像我相信的游戏中的 OSD。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm sure.
我相信。
Again,
再次，
you guys are silly.
你们真傻。
You guys are so silly.
你们太傻了
And why do coffee
以及为什么要喝咖啡
coffee?
咖啡？
I sure
我保证
muffle your song. All my alanine.
消音你的歌。 我所有的丙氨酸。
My throat was ready for mafia song today.
今天我的喉咙已经准备好听黑手党歌曲了。
I'll do one request.
我会做一个请求。
Sure.
当然。
Because I not
因为我不
why not?
为什么不？
Right.
对。
Everybody loves a little coffee
每个人都喜欢喝一点咖啡
I love coffee.
我爱咖啡。
You love coffee?
你喜欢咖啡吗？
Again.
再次。
Don't stay awake for too long.
不要保持清醒太久。
It's on. Go to bed.
它开着。 睡觉。
I'll make a cup of.
我会做一杯。
Coffee for your. Head.
咖啡给你。 头。
I'll get you up and go and out of bed.
我会扶你起来，然后起床。
And I promise that one day
我保证有一天
I'll feel fine
我会感觉很好
and then I promise that one day I'll feel
然后我保证有一天我会感觉很好
all right
and I'll make a cup of coffee
with the right amount of sugar.
我会用适量的糖煮一杯咖啡。
I lie.
我说谎了。
Yeah,
是的，
and I'll make a cup of coffee
with the right amount of sugar.
我会用适量的糖煮一杯咖啡。
How you like it?
你喜欢吗？
I know I can
我知道我可以
so now how long
所以现在多久
I'll stay for Itzhak?
我会为伊扎克留下吗？
Knock on your door.
敲你的门。
Won't you come down and get me.
你不下来接我吗？
I like when you call me I
我喜欢你叫我我
you make me feel nice
你让我感觉很好
The cream in your eyes makes me feel warm.
你眼中的乳霜让我感到温暖。
Inside I
里面我
And I'll.
我会的。
Make a cup.
做一个杯子。
Of coffee with the right.
咖啡的权利。
Amount The sugar I get
数量 我得到的糖
and I'll make a cup.
我会做一个杯子。
Of coffee with the.
的咖啡。
Right amount of sugar How will I get
适量的糖 我将如何获得
oh, you're like.
哦，你就像。
OK, there's your coffee.
好的，有你的咖啡。
There is your coffee.
有你的咖啡。
I love the I love this song
so I like it comes from the analogue.
我喜欢我喜欢这首歌，所以我喜欢它来自模拟。
People know it better from like the rap
that this was sampled from.
人们从采样的说唱中更好地了解它。
Right?
对？
Like this the.
像这样的。
Rap assembled this VI arm.
Rap 组装了这个 VI 臂。
And it's I just.
我只是。
Like chill chill vibes.
就像寒冷的寒冷氛围。
It is I sense so much
but I'll never get tired of it.
这是我的感觉，但我永远不会厌倦它。
And hey, it's kind of ironic, though.
嘿，不过，这有点讽刺。
I don't really drink coffee
like coffee for it's
我真的不像咖啡那样喝咖啡，因为它不像我不喝咖啡而且我喜欢这首歌。
not like I don't drink coffee
and e I like the song though.
I feel like I could go for a Oh yeah.
我觉得我可以去哦，是的。
Was it that awful gato thingy.
是不是那个可怕的加托事情。
I'll have to try one day.
我将不得不尝试一天。
That sounds really good.
这听起来真的很好。
I do that tomorrow.
我明天做。
You guys reminded me.
你们提醒了我。
I think I want to try. Hold on.
我想我想试试。 坚持，稍等。
I know what?
我知道什么？
I wanted to offer
some point coffee in there, but.
我想在那里提供一些点咖啡，但是。
This is a song that I think.
这是我认为的一首歌。
Everybody. Knows.
大家。 知道。
If you don't know this song, then
如果你不知道这首歌，那么
I feel like of what are you doing?
我感觉你在做什么？
It's so it's a very.
如此它是一个非常。
It's very simple,
这很简单，但我不知道。 一世
but I don't know. I
I wanted to try it here.
我想在这里试试。
Here, now.
现在这里。
As it comes from a good movie,
a really good movie
因为它来自一部好电影，我最喜欢的一部真正的好电影并不像，在这个分数上是公平的。
of one of my favourite ones are not like,
be fair on that score.
Jamal
贾马尔
bon as much type cock.
bon 尽可能多的类型的公鸡。
What am I doing
我在做什么
Eric? Go
埃里克? 去
you got.
你得到了。
A friend in me.
我里面的一个朋友。
You've got a friend in me.
你在我里面有一个朋友。
When the road looks
当前方的道路看起来崎岖不平，距离美好的地方数英里。
rough ahead and miles and miles from nice.
When did you just remember what your.
你什么时候才想起你的。
Old pal said?
老朋友说？
Boy, you've got a friend in me.
男孩，你有我的朋友。
Yeah, you've got a friend in me.
是的，你有我的朋友。
But da da da da da da
但是哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒哒
da da da da
you've got a friend in me
你有我的朋友
You've got a friend in me.
你在我里面有一个朋友。
You've got troubles.
你遇到了麻烦。
I got him too.
我也得到了他。
There isn't anything I.
我什么都没有。
Wouldn't do for you.
不会为你做的。
We stick together and see. It through
我们粘在一起看看。 它通过了，因为你有我的朋友
because you've got a friend in me
Yeah you've got a friend in me
是的，你有我的朋友
Some other folks
might be a little bit smarter than I am.
其他一些人可能比我聪明一点。
Bigger and stronger, too.
也更大更强。
But none of them will ever love you
the way that I do.
但他们都不会像我那样爱你。
It's me and you, boy.
是我和你，男孩。
And as the years gone by.
随着岁月的流逝。
Our friendship will never die.
我们的友谊永远不会消失。
You can see.
你可以看到。
It's our destiny Nay,
这是我们的命运 不，
you've got a friend in me.
你有我的朋友。
Yeah, you've.
是的，你有。
Got a friend in me.
我有一个朋友。
You've got a friend in me
你有我的朋友
The da da da.
哒哒哒。
Da da da da da da.
哒哒哒哒哒哒。
Oh. I love it so much.
哦。 我非常喜欢。
I love that song so much.
我非常喜欢那首歌。
It makes me want to rewatch Toy.
它让我想重温玩具。
Story.
故事。
Shot All Love Toy Story, huh?
射击所有爱情玩具总动员，是吗？
It's. Oh, it's a really grown man.
它的。 哦，真是个大人啊。
I don't think anyone can complain.
我认为没有人可以抱怨。
It's just a feel. It's.
这只是一种感觉。 它的。
Oh, it makes me.
哦，它让我。
Happy.
It's always something makes me happy, man.
快乐的。 这总是让我开心的事情，伙计。
As one of my first thoughts as Disney
movie still.
作为迪士尼电影的第一个想法之一。
All right.
好的。
Like, I don't think anybody hasn't.
就像，我认为没有人没有。
Seen Toy Story. Before. I.
看过玩具总动员。 前。 一世。
I don't know anyone who hasn't seen it
before.
我不知道有谁没有见过它。
Or, like, knows of it
or doesn't not know of it.
或者，例如，知道或不知道。
Am I freezing that
right? English? I don't know.
我冷冻对了吗？ 英语？ 我不知道。
You got a friend in me.
你在我里面有一个朋友。
You got a cock in me.
你有我的鸡巴。
OK, that's enough.
好的，这就够了。
Curse the content. Huh?
诅咒内容。 嗯？
So for these
所以对于这些
it's all for this next song.
这一切都是为了下一首歌。
So on
很快
oh, boy.
好家伙。
Well, now, knowing that no one heard that.
好吧，现在，知道没有人听到。
No one heard that.
没有人听说过。
Clip it out.
剪下来。
Clip it out to the other side.
把它夹到另一边。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You rhythm lads.
你们节奏小伙子。
You fool in the harnesses, don't you?
你在安全带上傻了，不是吗？
Oh, God.
天啊。
I don't think I. Can do it today.
我不认为我今天能做到。
Not to kick you.
不是为了踢你。
That's mean knock on who the he car game
这意味着敲他的汽车游戏或你的钥匙会在谁。
or your key meet in the.
And think I'm no match today.
并认为我今天不是对手。
I would really like to do it next time.
我真的很想下次再做。
I've done it before.
我以前做过。
We've done it
before. On the last karaoke session.
我们以前做过。 在最后的卡拉 OK 会议上。
When we had our white day or that. Yeah,
当我们有我们的白色情人节或那个。 是的，
but I think I'll
但我想我会
you know, we got like
你知道，我们还有两首我想做的歌。
two more songs that I want to do.
Yeah.
是的。
My God has already been almost two.
我的上帝已经快两岁了。
What the heck, guys?
什么鬼，伙计们？
It's three, almost 2 hours.
三个小时，差不多两个小时。
What's how
怎么样
got that.
知道了。
Down that flew by man.
从人那里飞下来。
Yeah, that really flew by so fast.
是的，它真的飞得太快了。
OK, then I'm going to switch over
to our last location night.
好的，那么我将切换到我们的最后一个地点晚上。
We're going to go somewhere else.
我们要去别的地方。
Let's get out this saw this little flower
我们出去看看这个小花田，樱花区。
field, the sakura blossom area.
I'm to take you somewhere else.
我要带你去别的地方。
OK, baby.
好的宝贝。
Mm hmm. Hmm.
嗯嗯。 唔。
OK, been here before.
好的，以前来过。
You guys remember?
大家还记得吗？
Right
对
and you hear that?
你听到了吗？
It's the,
ah, the crickets and all that stuff.
它是，啊，蟋蟀和所有的东西。
The moon, right?
月亮，对吧？
Yeah. You see that moon?
You see that moon?
是的。 你看到那个月亮了吗？ 你看到那个月亮了吗？
If you can guess what I'm guessing
next, huh?
如果你能猜到我接下来会猜什么，嗯？
Yes. I'm guessing next.
是的。 我猜接下来。
I'm going to give you a little bit
of a different flair this time, though.
不过，这次我要给你一点不同的天赋。
Usually I do it like for.
通常我喜欢这样做。
Me to them
我对他们
me play amongst the stars.
我在群星中玩耍。
But I want to try a little.
但我想尝试一下。
I want to try something different
this time.
这次我想尝试一些不同的东西。
OK, bear with me.
好吧，忍耐一下。
Now, bear with me for a second.
现在，请容忍我一秒钟。
I'm going to do something
我要做点什么
non-conventional
非传统
all right.
好的。
Well, I don't butcher this
好吧，我不屠宰这个
I wish me luck.
我祝我好运。
The sexier version.
更性感的版本。
What do you mean, the sexier version?
你是什​​么意思，更性感的版本？
Fly me to the moon
带我去月球
and let me play amongst the stars.
让我在群星之间玩耍。
Lemme see what spring is like.
让我看看春天是什么样的。
Jupiter serving Mars another.
木星服务火星另一个。
But hold my hand. Hmm.
但是握住我的手。 唔。
Another way it's a baby.
另一种方式是婴儿。
Kiss me and
吻我和
fill my heart with song
用歌声填满我的心 让思念永远歌唱
and let miss sing for evermore
You will love our love Long for
你会爱上我们的爱渴望所有的爱崇拜和锯
all love worship and the saw
and not the words
而不是这些话
Please be true
请真实
Enough though Why
虽然够了 为什么
I love you
我爱你
Fill my heart with song
用歌声填满我的心
And let me say for evermore
让我永远说
are love long for a love worship
爱情渴望爱情崇拜吗
and that song And though I
还有那首歌 虽然我
please be true
请真实
another way it's
另一种方式
in other words In other words
换句话说 换句话说
I love you
我爱你
Oh ha ha.
哦哈哈。
Oh you did it
哦，到目前为止，你都做到了。
all so far.
And that was the violence in L.A.
这就是洛杉矶的暴力事件。
more often.
更频繁。
I don't I don't really do.
我没有我真的没有。
All that all that extra flair to it
because I just like to keep it simple.
所有这一切都赋予它额外的天赋，因为我只是喜欢保持简单。
But I want to try a different,
you know, style of singing it.
但我想尝试一种不同的，你知道的，唱它的风格。
Let me play amongst the stars.
让我在星星之间玩耍。
That was amazing.
那太精彩了。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You like jazz?
你喜欢爵士乐吗？
Don't really said gunshot. OK,
不要真的说枪声。 好吧，这很有趣，对吧？
it's a lot of fun, right?
I think that's the point of our guys.
我认为这是我们球员的重点。
That's the point of karaoke. You know,
这就是卡拉OK的意义所在。 你知道，
is got to have fun with it.
一定要玩得开心。
You have to have fun with it.
你必须玩得开心。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
I'm not having fun with it.
我不喜欢它。
Then what's the point right?
那有什么意义呢？
Yeah.
是的。
I also hope that you guys
can feel my joy from over there.
我也希望你们能从那里感受到我的快乐。
I like I mean, like you're right
next to me.
我喜欢我的意思是，就像你就在我身边一样。
We're holding hands.
我们手牵手。
I mean, what are.
我的意思是，是什么。
So this next song
所以下一首歌
is going to be.
将是。
Our last song for the night
我们今晚的最后一首歌
it's.
它的。
Yeah, this is going to be our last one.
是的，这将是我们的最后一个。
And I think we're going to wrap it up
there and just have a small chill
我想我们会把它包起来，在结束之前稍微放松一下。
before we end it off.
2 hours went by so fast, guys.
2小时过得真快，伙计们。
You really did. Wow.
你真的做到了。 哇。
But everything I've said before,
I really does hope.
但我之前所说的一切，我真的希望。
I hope that rings true and that you guys
hold it near and dear to your dear hearts.
我希望这听起来是真的，并且你们把它放在你们亲爱的心上。
Because, I mean, what I said
因为，我的意思是，我在下一首歌中所说的话对每个人和
this next song holds
the weight of my feelings to each and
every one of you and to the
你们每一个人和未来的公会成员，加入我们的家，品尝一些样品。
future guild members that join our home
in some sample for a bite.
I want to sing it again
since it has a special meaning to me.
我想再唱一遍，因为它对我有特殊的意义。
And there's a lyric in the song
that translates roughly to
歌曲中有一句歌词大致翻译为
I'll pluck the stars from the sky
and give them to you,
我会摘下天上的星星给你，
my galaxy and
我的银河系和
I never
我从不
like to think much about the future
喜欢多想未来
because. I'm.
因为。 我是。
I'm a person that loves to live
in the moments
我是一个喜欢活在当下并享受今天的人，而不是一直担心一些事情。
and enjoy today rather than worry
about some all all the time.
But I know that there will be battles,
但我知道，不仅对我，而且对我们所有人，都会有战斗、斗争和障碍。
struggles and obstacles for not only me,
but for all of us.
And I mean, that's normal in the quest,
right?
我的意思是，这在任务中很正常，对吧？
In any journey or adventure, it's
never a straight line.
在任何旅程或冒险中，它从来都不是一条直线。
There's always some type of
总有某种类型
network like this.
像这样的网络。
There's always some type of monster
or side quest or mini boss or chops
我们总会遇到某种类型的怪物或支线任务或迷你老板或排骨。
we fall into.
But that's why
we called an adventure. Right?
但这就是为什么我们称之为冒险。 对？
And that's all you guys are part of.
这就是你们的一部分。
My no part of our.
我不属于我们。
Adventure scaled, and I'm
冒险规模扩大，我在成长，我在学习。
growing and I'm learning.
I'm expanding my skill tree
all the time, every day.
我每天都在扩展我的技能树。
And I really want to be a better person
every single day.
我真的很想每天都成为一个更好的人。
And I know I won't be.
我知道我不会。
Able to please everybody, but.
能够取悦所有人，但是。
I've never.
我从来没有。
Had such a
有过这样一个
I've never had such a strong desire
我从未有过如此强烈的欲望
to make myself
让自己
a better version of myself
比昨天更好的自己。
than I was yesterday before.
And so I met all of you guys
所以我遇到了你们所有人和我所有珍贵的朋友。 和，
and all my precious friends. And,
I mean, I'm still young as hell,
and I'm still trying to learn the world.
我的意思是，我还很年轻，我还在努力学习这个世界。
And, I mean, we all are in some way,
whether we're ten, 20, 50, or even like
而且，我的意思是，我们都在某种程度上，无论我们是
10 岁、20 岁、50 岁，还是像
206 year old elves.
206岁的精灵。
If you guys are out there by
如果你们在外面
I. I.
我，我。
I want to try and
我想尝试成为灵感
be an inspiration
to as many people as I can,
and it feels like
尽可能多的人，感觉就像
that's my duty
as your guild leader as well.
这也是我作为你们公会会长的职责。
And I want to help you all realise
how far you can go as well and
我想帮助你们所有人意识到你们还能走多远
to be at your happiest.
在你最快乐的时候。
And I hope I can help you guys get there
我希望我能帮助你们实现目标
and realise it
This next song is called Galaxy
下一首歌叫 Galaxy
Song and before and that song.
歌曲和之前和那首歌。
It's a good one.
这是一个很好的。
I love it so much.
我非常喜欢。
Galaxy.
星系。
Yes, remember that, right?
是的，记住了，对吧？
커피를 너무
看来是喝了
많이 마셨나 봐요
太多咖啡
심장이 막 두근대고
心脏扑通个不停
잠은 잘
不能好好入睡
수가 없어요 한참 뒤에 별빛이 내리면
在这之后星光洒落的话
난 다시 잠들 순 없겠죠
我又会无法入睡了吧
지나간 새벽을 다 새면
当黎明破晓时
다시 네 곁에 잠들겠죠
会再次在你身边入睡吧
너의 품에 잠든 난 마치 천사가 된 것만 같아요
在你怀里睡着的我就像变成了天使一样
난 그대 품에 별빛을
我在你怀里
쏟아 내리고
星光倾落下来
은하수를 만들어 어디든
打造了银河
날아가게 할거야
可以到处飞翔
Cause I'm a pilot anywhere Cause I'm a pilot anywhere
因为我是一名飞行员,我无处不在
Lighting star shooting star
闪烁的星星，划过的流星
줄게 내 galaxy Cause I'm a pilot anywhere
给你 我的宇宙（银河）
because I'm a pilot anywhere Kazaam
Cause I'm your pilot 네 곁에 저 별을 따
因为我是你的飞行员 在你身边 摘下那颗星星
네게만 줄게 my galaxy
只给你 我的宇宙（银河）
La la da da
啦啦哒哒哒哒
da da
la la da.
啦啦啦
Da da di.
哒哒哒。
La di da.
拉哒达。
줄게 내 galaxy
只给你我的银河
어제는 내가
昨天我的
기분이 참 좋아서
心情好好
지나간 행성에다가 그대 이름 새겨 놓았죠
在略过的行星上 刻下了你的名字
한참 뒤에 별빛이 내리면
在这之后星光洒落的话
그 별이 가장 밝게 빛
那颗星星最为耀眼
나요 지나간 새벽을
当黎明破晓时
다 새면 다시 네 곁에 잠들겠죠
会再次在你身边入睡吧
별빛 아래 잠든 난
在星光下睡着的我
마치 온 우주를 가진 것만 같아
就像拥有了全世界一样
난 그대 품에 별빛을 쏟아 내리고
我在你的怀里 星光倾落下来
은하수를 만들어
打造了银河
어디든 날아가게 할거야
可以到处飞翔
Cause I'm
因为我是
a pilot anywhere Cause I'm a pilot anywhere
飞行员，我无处不在
Lighting star shooting star
闪烁的星星，划过的流星
줄게 내 galaxy Cause I'm a pilot anywhere
给你 我的宇宙（银河） 因为我是飞行员
Cause I'm your pilot 네 곁에
因为我是你的飞行员 在你身边
저 별을 따 네게만 줄게 my galaxy
摘下那颗星星 只给你 我的宇宙
Cause I'm a pilot anywhere Cause I'm a pilot anywhere
因为我是飞行员，我无处不在
Lighting star shooting star
闪烁的星星，划过的流星
줄게 내 galaxy
给你 我的宇宙
Cause I'm a pilot
因为我是飞行员
I'm your pilot
因为我是你的飞行员
lighting star shooting star 줄게
闪烁的星星，划过的流星
my galaxy
只给你 我的宇宙
라라라라라
啦啦啦啦啦。
啦啦啦 拉
But I didn't
但我没有
I, I the I'm not going to lie the
我，我我不会说谎的
the high note was kind of a for flavour.
高音是一种风味。
I, I didn't know how
all that was going to go. I.
我，我不知道这一切会怎样。 一世。
I just felt like doing it.
我只是觉得想做。
And um, it kind of. Works I mean I.
嗯，有点。 作品我的意思是我。
I really
我真的嗯，我非常喜欢这首歌，就像女孩我一样
um, I like that song like girl me so much
and I'm glad I gets to feel
that comfortable with song so fast.
我很高兴我能这么快就对这首歌感到舒服。
They can like, you know, free.
他们可以喜欢，你知道，免费的。
Myself.
我。
Oh man.
天啊。
I really
我真的
I feel so lucky to have
我觉得很幸运有
all of you here and
你们所有人都在这里，很可能是最好的社区的恩典
be grace
by for quite possibly the best community
I could ever ask for.
我可以要求。
Yeah.
是的。
I love my guilty so much
我非常爱我的罪孽
thank you so much for listening.
非常感谢您的聆听。
So all my songs.
所以我所有的歌曲。
Yeah, that was my last one.
是的，那是我的最后一个。
I don't want to overdo it.
我不想做得过火。
I can feel like again I can feel my throat
getting a little bit raspy.
我可以再次感觉到我的喉咙变得有点刺耳。
And at that point,
I think it's better to just, like,
在那一点上，我认为最好只是，喜欢，
hold it there and not, you know,
坚持住，不要，你知道，做任何事
overdo anything
so I feel like
if I overdo it, it's not all that good.
所以我觉得如果我做得过头了，那并不是那么好。
I don't wanna.
我不想。
Have we have to.
我们有没有必要。
Stream tomorrow, too, so I don't know.
明天也直播，所以不知道。
I like
我喜欢
wrecking myself.
破坏自己。
Yeah.
是的。
It's never
它从来不是
it's never a good idea to overdo it, guys.
伙计们，过度使用从来都不是一个好主意。
Never a good idea.
从来不是一个好主意。
For all, though.
不过，对所有人来说。
I thank you so much for listening to all
my songs and every word and everything.
我非常感谢你听我所有的歌，每一个字，每件事。
I said meet me. I mean it.
我说见我。 我是认真的。
I really do want to try my best
and I hope that
我真的很想尽我所能，我希望
I can
我可以
continue to be an inspiration
for so many of you
继续成为你们许多人的灵感来源
and to show you, like, how
向你展示，就像，多么美妙
wonderful
you guys are as well. You've sing.
你们也是。 你有唱。
I like, I'm this,
我喜欢，我就是这样，
like, lovely or like amazing person, but
喜欢，可爱或喜欢惊人的人，但看看你们，好吗？
look at you guys, all right?
That you guys mm.
那你们mm。
Yeah.
是的。
That concludes our karaoke session
for the night.
我们晚上的卡拉OK会议到此结束。
I'm gonna switch on over
我要重新开启
switch on over to
切换到
the bedroom
and just, like, have a small chill.
卧室，就像，有一个小寒意。
So give me a quick
moment, all right? I'm gonna
所以给我一点时间，好吗？ 我将要
be back in, like, a minute or so.
回来，就像，一分钟左右。
I'm going to grab myself a quick drink.
我要给自己快速喝一杯。
Uh, I think I'll get myself.
呃，我想我会得到自己的。
Yeah, soju.
对，烧酒。
My soju. OK, baby,
我的烧酒。 好的，宝贝，给我一秒钟。
give me a second.
Now let's use the bathroom because.
现在让我们使用浴室，因为。
Oh, my God, I drink so much water today.
天哪，我今天喝了这么多水。
I drink so much. Voila.
我喝这么多。 瞧。
I'll I'll read through all of the.
我会我会通读所有的。
Donations and all the sobs
and all the bits during the during
捐赠和所有的啜泣和所有的点点滴滴在晚会期间。
the after party.
OK, so baby, give me one second
好的，所以宝贝，给我一秒钟
yeah.
是的。
Well, I copy
嗯，我复制
it's like a Polaroid, love.
它就像宝丽来，亲爱的。
It's not there.
它不在那里。
Just sit on. Good guy.
就坐吧。 好小子。
I'm just kind and guy Sinatra.
我只是一个善良的家伙西纳特拉。
But now now
但现在现在
listen.
听。
I am man and got you.
我是男人，得到了你。
A tap on gum.
轻按口香糖。
Johnny's in the mood.
约翰尼心情不错。
Tell me that.
告诉我。
I could go back to them.
我可以回到他们身边。
Tonguing up
吐舌头
when you
当你
kiss good,
吻得好，
it's like a shot and
这就像一个镜头
then like a big
然后像一个大
yeah.
是的。
Know you
知道你
on it, Gina.
就在上面，吉娜。
Boy, I
男孩，我
sure to
一定要
imagine
想象
numb. Now.
麻木的。 现在。
The lower down the music a bit.
音乐低了一点。
I guys, I'm back.
伙计们，我回来了。
Yeah, you missed me.
是的，你想我了。
Of course you did.
你当然做到了。
Didn't, did, did, didn't.
没有，没有，没有，没有。
I don't know what I said there to you.
我不知道我在那里对你说了什么。
I'll come back.
我会回来。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank y'all. Love I.
谢谢大家。 爱我。
I got myself a little,
a small little beverage.
我给自己弄了一点，一点点小饮料。
Not a big cluster.
不是一个大集群。
Yeah.
是的。
To soar to some peaches
you I've had left over from us.
翱翔到我从我们那里留下的一些桃子。
The voice is so charming.
声音太迷人了。
We are proud of you.
我们以你为荣。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
All of you guys
enjoyed all the songs tonight.
你们所有人都喜欢今晚的所有歌曲。
Do you.
你。
Have a favourite out of all of them.
有一个最喜欢的。
Like we've done so many.
就像我们做了很多一样。
Good morning show love from HK all
早安表达来自香港的爱
300 K on Twitch
I will have an exam within five.
Twitch 上 300 K 我将在五分钟内参加考试。
Good morning.
早上好。
What's your major in college?
你大学的专业是什么？
Oh. I don't think I'm a
哦。 我不认为我是一个
I don't think I cannot say that,
but I'll keep that, you know, to myself.
我不认为我不能这么说，但我会保留，你知道，对我自己。
But have a good morning. Ziadeh,
thank you for coming by.
但祝你早上好。  Ziadeh，谢谢你的光临。
Well, ok.
好吧，好吧。
I promised that I
我保证会通读所有内容。
would read through all of the what's it.
Through all. Of the
通过所有。 捐赠等权利。
donations and such right.
Now, give me a second.
现在，给我一秒钟。
Because wow, there's a lot of.
因为哇，有很多。
There's a lot of them ends are
I feel bad that I think lets us
有很多结局是我感觉不好，我想让我们在直播中说任何话。
say anything during the stream.
I just want to keep it's
focussed on the music and the singing.
我只是想让它专注于音乐和歌唱。
Thanks so much for sharing your story
and time with us.
非常感谢您与我们分享您的故事和时间。
You really have to tug
at our heartstrings.
你真的必须拉动我们的心弦。
Very much appreciated
and loved by your community.
非常受到您的社区的赞赏和喜爱。
Also, congrats on the milestones.
另外，祝贺里程碑。
Keep plugging on.
继续插电。
Keep logging on. I like that.
继续登录。 我喜欢。
Thank you so much, bro.
太谢谢你了，兄弟。
Ah, suki, thank you for the five time
gif subs a little more.
啊，suki，谢谢你的五次 gif 潜艇多一点。
Thank you for the donation.
感谢您的捐赠。
So happy to see you progressing, babe.
很高兴看到你进步，宝贝。
The reason you dropped off
your son is because of your voice.
你放弃儿子的原因是因为你的声音。
But reasons I say is you, sweetie.
但我说的原因是你，亲爱的。
I really.
我真的。
Everybody says, like.
大家都说，喜欢。
The reason why people stay or, like,
enjoy.
人们留下或喜欢享受的原因。
Like, it doesn't matter.
喜欢，没关系。
The game, it like the game or the
what we're doing oh.
游戏，它喜欢游戏或者我们正在做的事情哦。
Let's keep growing our boys.
让我们的孩子继续成长。
I think people enjoy, like,
you know, just the the person.
我认为人们喜欢，就像，你知道的，只是那个人。
But I don't know.
但是我不知道。
I guess I struggle to, like, accept
that sometimes because it's like.
我想我有时很难接受，因为它就像。
Sometimes, like.
有时，像。
Sometimes I think, like, I. Really
I don't know if.
有时我想，就像，我。真的我不知道。
I'm doing enough for you guys and I.
我为你们和我做的已经够多了。
I keep wanting to do more, but
我一直想做更多，但是
it's, it's like, you know,
它就像，你知道，
I think everyone in my friends can relate,
so there's like,
我认为我朋友中的每个人都可以联系起来，所以就像，
that internal, like, struggle, like,
am I doing enough and what's going enough?
那种内心的，喜欢，挣扎，喜欢，我做得够不够，什么做得够好？
So I always want to try and do
as much as I can for everybody.
所以我总是想为每个人尽我所能。
We are lazy.
我们很懒惰。
Thank you for the I don't know.
Thank you for everything, pumpkin.
谢谢你的我不知道。 谢谢你所做的一切，南瓜。
You always bring a smile to my face
one eye and make me laugh when it's own.
你总是给我的一只眼睛带来微笑，当它是自己的时候让我笑。
Oh, I'm glad I can bring
a smile on their face and.
哦，我很高兴我能给他们带来微笑。
Knowing that.
知道。
Somebody laughs from my dreams still is.
仍然有人从我的梦中笑出来。
You know it means the world to me.
你知道这对我来说意味着整个世界。
Galaxy.
星系。
Yeah, I really like
Galaxy was a really fun time.
是的，我真的很喜欢 Galaxy 是一段非常有趣的时光。
Then I. Got I want to sing more dry.
然后我。我想唱得更干。
Flower. Dry flowers.
花。 干花。
Such a good song, man.
这么好的歌，伙计。
Uh, I'm really, like, happy.
嗯，我真的很高兴。
I learnt about it.
我了解到了。
Thank you for the wonderful karaoke
tonight. Hmm.
谢谢你今晚精彩的卡拉OK。 唔。
I love you.
我爱你。
I love you guys still. Yeah,
我依然爱你们。 是的，
I go.
我去。
Cause I'm
因为我是
not. Yeah, I thought
不是。 是的，我没想过废话，废话，废话。
not about blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
是的。
I was really vibing off far dry flower
我真的很喜欢远干燥的花朵
along. Give me a. Second.
沿着。 给我一个。 第二。
CC Oh, cc, thank you for that's all.
CC 哦，cc，谢谢你。
Now it thank you for the tell
no and zacky.
现在它感谢你告诉不和 zacky。
Thank you for this.
I know this is your first.
这次真是万分感谢。 我知道这是你的第一次。
I know
我知道你今天过得很糟糕，但听你唱歌给了我力量。
you were really having a bad day today,
but hearing you sing gives me strength.
And comfort
和舒适
or for all
或为所有人
that.
那。
I will continue to always support
you and I look for.
我将继续永远支持你，我正在寻找。
It's history. Me too.
这是历史。 我也是。
I love you, shuttle. Congrats on three.
我爱你，穿梭。 恭喜三连。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Thank you guys so much.
非常感谢你们。
I was looking complimented.
我看起来很恭维。
For my singing. It's just like,
man, you're making.
为了我的歌声。 就像，伙计，你在做。
You're making a young boy very happy.
你让一个小男孩很开心。
And inside me, there's a young boy
在我的内心，有一个小男孩一直想要，就像，你知道的，有人认可，像，
who has always wanted, like,
you know, someone to recognise, like,
their efforts to, like, sing better
and, like, try better at singing.
他们努力，喜欢，唱得更好，喜欢，尝试唱得更好。
And he's like very much elated right now
and, like, having the time of his life.
他现在非常兴高采烈，就像，享受他生命中的时光。
Thanks to you guys. Congratulations.
谢谢你们。 恭喜。
I love your singing so much.
我非常喜欢你的歌声。
Keep going. We'll always stay with you.
继续前进。 我们将永远与您同在。
Love you.
爱你。
Move, move, move.
动，动，动。
Move, move.
动，动。
Thank you
any for the big dance now as well.
也感谢你们现在的大舞会。
Thank you for this honour, too.
也谢谢你的这份荣誉。
You're thinking someday for this this.
你总有一天会为此考虑。
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎哎
Somewhere I think there's this talk about
an s summer club.
在某个地方，我认为有关于夏季俱乐部的讨论。
I'll try and read that later.
我稍后会尝试阅读。
Sorry. Thank you for. That's l know.
对不起。 谢谢你。 那是我知道的。
Glad to have such
an unforgettable experience.
很高兴有这样一次难忘的经历。
If you.
如果你。
Oh, you got me velvety.
哦，你让我变得柔软。
Shut out now.
现在关掉。
You and that's cheesy.
你这很俗气。
Hi, Sholto.
嗨，肖尔托。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
On the 300
K on twitch and 400 K on twitter.
在 twitch 上的 300 K
和 twitter 上的 400 K。
Thank you for appearing in my life.
谢谢你出现在我的生命里。
Thank you for the karaoke stream.
感谢您提供卡拉 OK 直播。
I really enjoyed it.
我真的很喜欢。
I love you so much.
我真的很爱你。
And I'm always on your side.
而我永远站在你这边。
Guys, I'm going to I'm going to write.
伙计们，我要去我要去写。
I like I want to.
我喜欢我想。
Grab your guys is like by the scruff.
抓住你的家伙就像是在脖子上。
Give you a little kiss on the cheek
and toss you in.
在你的脸颊上轻轻吻一下，然后把你扔进去。
So, like, I don't know
until like a field of flowers.
所以，喜欢，直到喜欢一片花田才知道。
I'm not think of it.
我没有想到。
It's ancient. Sorry. Your voice
so comfy that I actually fell asleep.
它是古老的。 对不起。 你的声音好舒服，我真的睡着了。
Yeah, I have important interview.
是的，我有重要的采访。
And today, please lend me a little
good luck.
今天，请借给我一点好运。
Good luck to you.
You got this? I believe in you.
祝你好运。 你有这个吗？ 我相信你。
All right.
好的。
Guys, what?
伙计们，什么？
You got this, bro?
你有这个，兄弟？
Asuka, thank you for the doll.
明日香，谢谢你的娃娃。
Now, a sort of subtle softball.
现在，一种微妙的垒球。
I love you.
我爱你。
Thank you for your sweet singing
谢谢你甜美的歌声
from him, bro.
从他那里，兄弟。
I hope I can do more karaoke.
我希望我能做更多的卡拉OK。
In the future for everybody.
未来为大家。
This one was supposed to be
a very special occasion, and I hope
这应该是一个非常特殊的场合，我希望
we can do another one probably next month
or in the couple of months after.
我们可能会在下个月或之后的几个月内再做一次。
You know, I practise some more songs
你知道，我练习了更多的歌曲
oh. I'm going to go back and read through
哦。 我要回去阅读亚洲钢铁公司的一些早期广告以及最近的一些广告。
some of the earlier ads on Asian
Steel and stuff like the most recent ones.
Coffee. Thank you for the resolver.
咖啡。 谢谢你的解析器。
Welcome back.
And I hope you've been doing well, bro.
欢迎回来。 我希望你一直做得很好，兄弟。
Where is it?
它在哪里？
I am. I'm stupid.
我是。 我很蠢。
I'm stupid. Where is it?
我很蠢。 它在哪里？
I know
我知道
my dumb boy.
我的笨孩子。
I'm a fucking dumb boy.
我是个他妈的傻孩子。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Here it is.
这里是。
All right,
好的，
euphoria.
欣快感。
Thank you for the.
谢谢你的。
Odds on our gum,
but the thank you so much.
我们口香糖的赔率，但非常感谢你。
And that's it.
就是这样。
Ah! Oh, my God.
啊! 我的天啊。
Machida, what's
町田，什么
all this shit?
所有这些狗屎？
Thank you for the 1000
谢谢你的1000
1000.
1000。
Oh, Mike.
哦，迈克。
Dude, what the fuck?
哥们儿，什么鬼？
I don't.
我不。
I don't know. With the holy shit, dude.
我不知道。 与神圣的狗屎，伙计。
I'm like, oh, that's.
我想，哦，就是这样。
That's a lot of.
那是很多。
Yeah, that's a lot of money.
是的，那是很多钱。
Are you. Sure?
你是。 当然？
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
I, I, I.
我，我，我。
I oh.
我哦。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
That's a very big deal.
这是一件大事。
No, dude, I
不，伙计，我
thank you so much.
太感谢了。
I hope you are.
我希望你是。
I hope you're able to,
you know, feed yourself.
我希望你能够，你知道的，养活自己。
And, you know, enjoy your.
而且，你知道，享受你的。
Treat yourself as well.
也善待自己。
I don't give too much to me. OK?
我不会给我太多。 好的？
I really do appreciate it, though.
Thank you so much.
不过，我真的很感激。 非常感谢。
But I really hope that, you know,
但我真的希望，你知道，你也过得很好，而且，你知道，你在照顾好自己。
you're well off, too, and that, you know,
you're taking care of yourself.
Bro, it means a lot. Thank you.
兄弟，意义重大。 谢谢你。
You, too.
你也是。
You're been such a big supporter
of the Charlottesville.
你一直是夏洛茨维尔的忠实支持者。
It means like the world to me
that you continue to do so
这对我来说意味着就像世界一样，你继续这样做
and so support not only me, but
所以不仅支持我，而且
the guilds as well.
公会也是。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
I'd love
我很乐意
to see you. And you are.
为了见你。 而你是。
Thank you for.
谢谢你。
The 1000 berries.
1000 个浆果。
Can graduation.
可以毕业。
Can graduation. Congratulations.
可以毕业。 恭喜。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Overall,
and another year for the five johns.
总体而言，五位约翰再过一年。
Thank you for the $3.
谢谢你的 3 美元。
Golly, Gail, thank you for that.
天哪，盖尔，谢谢你。
Sincerely and yourselves.
真诚的和你们自己。
Your supporters.
你的支持者。
Thank you for that.
谢谢你。
Well, now, congrats on for an education.
好吧，现在，恭喜你接受了教育。
We plan to set up a pa pa pa pa
我们计划成立一个 pa pa pa pa
You want a name for your group?
你想为你的小组取个名字吗？
Mm. Shuttles, wolf squad.
毫米。 穿梭机，狼队。
Oh, that sounds funny.
哦，这听起来很有趣。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Shuttle's Wolf Squad.
穿梭的狼队。
I don't know something.
我不知道什么。
Hmm. You guys got.
唔。 你们得到了。
I don't.
我不。
I don't know. What I would say. Huh.
我不知道。 我想说什么。 嗯。
Sounds like a funny name.
听起来是个有趣的名字。
Wolf.
狼。
I'm not dog, though.
不过，我不是狗。
It sounds. You know, just
听起来。 你知道，只是因为，就像我每次都说的那样，
because, like I say this every time,
just because I bark, because I know.
只是因为我吠叫，因为我知道。
Because I.
因为我。
You know, it doesn't mean I'm a dog.
你知道，这并不意味着我是一条狗。
Do you see ears anywhere?
I don't think so.
你在任何地方看到耳朵吗？ 我不这么认为。
And you guys can't put any ears.
而且你们不能竖起耳朵。
On me tonight
because I turn it off. So get. Direct.
今晚在我身上，因为我把它关掉了。 所以得到。 直接的。
Yogi.
瑜伽士。
Thank you for the honour.
谢谢你的荣誉。
So are we listening to your stream
and class?
那么我们在听你的直播和课程吗？
Is your first time
catching up your karaoke?
你是第一次追上你的卡拉OK吗？
Oh, OK. Lack of class, dude.
哦好的。 缺课，伙计。
Pay attention in class. Don't.
在班上注意听讲。 不。
Guys, guys.
伙计们，伙计们。
Pay attention, class. OK,
注意，上课。 好的，
I thank you for the ads.
我感谢你的广告。
Oh, no.
不好了。
And see what else.
看看还有什么。
And Zorn, thank you for the 1000 bits.
还有 Zorn，谢谢你的 1000 位。
Take these big.
Skipping, amazing shot, bull.
拿这些大的。 跳跃，惊人的射门，公牛。
Thank you so much, man.
非常感谢你，伙计。
I hope you enjoyed the songs
in the karaoke, Wolf.
我希望你喜欢卡拉 OK 中的歌曲，Wolf。
Sure.
当然。
Right.
对。
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
I'm just drinking casually at the moment,
我现在只是随便喝酒，所以不是那么多。
so that's not so much.
Reverend, thank you for the honour, Sean.
牧师，谢谢你的荣幸，肖恩。
Thank you for it. That's all now.
谢谢你。 现在就是这样。
Yeah, I was really nervous.
是的，我真的很紧张。
They'll be so nervous.
他们会很紧张。
You say you actually live.
I said you're very careful.
你说你真的活着。 我说你很小心。
Your mom said I was cute.
你妈妈说我很可爱。
Your mom approves of me. Wow.
你妈妈认可我。 哇。
Ha, ha. Wow.
哈哈。 哇。
Do your guys's moms approve of me?
你男朋友的妈妈同意我吗？
Do your parents approve of me?
你父母同意我吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Maybe I'm not.
也许我不是。
So I'm not like a doctor.
所以我不像医生。
I'm lawyer enough for some people.
对于某些人来说，我是一名律师。
I know.
我知道。
My my my parents are like that. I'm
pretty sure my parents are like, that.
我我我爸妈就是这样。 我很确定我的父母就是这样的。
So it's called. It's called. Asian.
所以被称为。 它被称为。 亚洲人。
Asian life breath.
亚洲生活气息。
OK. It's always.
好的。 总是如此。
It's always like oh, like what?
它总是像哦，像什么？
How how much money does he have?
他有多少钱？
How how is he handsome?
他怎么帅？
Is he tall?
他高吗？
How can he support this family?
他怎么能养活这个家庭？
Right.
对。
It's always
I feel like it's always that kind of.
我总是觉得它总是那样。
Like mentality
when it comes to appearance. It's like.
喜欢外表的心态。 它像是。
Oh, what can he give you?
哦，他能给你什么？
Or like, what can he give us, too?
或者像，他也能给我们什么？
Right.
对。
It's so.
就是这样。
Dumb.
哑的。
I'll miss the thank.
我会想念谢谢。
That's for that.
那就是为了那个。
Ali, thank you for the talent, though.
阿里，不过，谢谢你的才华。
And Kyra,
and thank you for the gifts, jobs.
还有凯拉，谢谢你的礼物和工作。
And I am thank you for the 50 50.
我感谢你的 50 50。
It's your one gifts, jobs.
这是您的一份礼物，一份工作。
I think you give like a hundred
yum or I am.
我想你给一百个百胜，或者我是。
Thank you so much for the 100 gifts
I was Rowan's I really hope
非常感谢我送给 Rowan 的 100
that the karaoke you know was
that's your it's your pleasure and taste.
份礼物，我真的希望你知道的卡拉
OK 是你的，这是你的乐趣和品味。
And another I'm sorry I.
还有一个对不起我。
Got seriously
but thank you so much for the raid Yana.
认真但非常感谢你的突袭雅娜。
Well, if you're still here
and if you are, then the
好吧，如果你还在这里，如果你还在，那么
operation was good.
操作很好。
And I hope you're having a great night
so far.
我希望你到目前为止度过了一个愉快的夜晚。
Pinky, thank you for the doll.
小指，谢谢你的娃娃。
No, starting each with its own now
and something for that's all.
不，从现在开始每个都有自己的东西，仅此而已。
Know a star like that guy from Black
认识一个像黑人一样的明星
Clover, a star or ask the he stuff.
三叶草，一星还是问他的东东。
It's like it's all a so it's like,
you know how.
就像一切都是这样，你知道怎么做。
Aaron has a double A and you say like
Aaron or some people say Aaron, I guess.
Aaron 有一个双 A，你说像
Aaron 或者有人说 Aaron，我猜。
It's I call you. A star or.
是我给你打电话。 一颗星或。
You're a star.
你是明星。
A star. I don't know
一个明星。 我不知道
any. Thank you for the attendance
you're on yourselves.
任何。 感谢您亲自出席。
And Hepner is.
赫普纳是。
Good morning. Well,
thank you for that solitaire on gift subs.
早上好。 好吧，谢谢你在礼物潜艇上的纸牌。
And Cindy thank you for that's on the on
thank you for the.
和 Cindy，谢谢你就在上，谢谢你。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, my God. My thing refreshed.
我的天啊。 我的东西焕然一新。
I lost track of where it was
我不知道它在哪里
a cat. Thank you for.
一只猫。 谢谢你。
That's Elmo and Lauren.
那是埃尔莫和劳伦。
Thank you for the tickets.
You're on guest subs.
谢谢你的票。 你在客人潜艇上。
Just thank you for the throwing
gifts of still why are you so cute?
只是谢谢你扔的礼物，你为什么这么可爱？
This explain explain.
这个解释解释。
What do you mean?
Why am I so cute? What? How, huh?
你什么意思？ 为什么我这么可爱？ 什么？ 怎么样，嗯？
What am I doing right now?
我现在在做什么？
That is so cute, huh?
太可爱了吧？
I'm just reading
我只是在阅读
just thank you for the 30.
只是谢谢你的30。
01 I. Subs. By the way, I saw ads.
01 一世。 顺便说一句，我看到了广告。
On a message that says like,
sorry I can't donate much as of lately.
在一条消息上说，对不起，我最近不能捐赠太多。
Don't ever never.
永远不要。
Apologise for that.
为此道歉。
OK, that's the last thing I want
you guys to do.
好的，这是我希望你们做的最后一件事。
You guys watching.
各位围观。
And just being here.
就在这里。
Is doing so much more than than
like you can imagine.
所做的比你想象的要多得多。
Donating is just is.
捐赠就是这样。
Always an option. OK.
永远是一个选择。 好的。
Please, like, don't give me.
请喜欢，不要给我。
Anything if you're having a hard time
or don't like feel like you.
如果您遇到困难或不喜欢自己的感觉。
Have to
please just think about yourselves.
必须请考虑一下自己。
Treat yourself so like some ice cream,
you know I'm gonna do tomorrow
像对待冰淇淋一样对待自己，你知道我明天要做
I'm going to go give myself
some strawberry and cheesecake ice cream.
我要去给自己一些草莓和芝士蛋糕冰淇淋。
I think you guys should do. The same,
all right?
我认为你们应该这样做。 一样的，好吗？
Instead of, like,
而不是，比如，你知道，给我一些东西，你知道，如果你只是让我更快乐。
you know, given something to me,
you know, make me happier if you just.
Think about.
想一想。
Yourselves once in a while as well.
自己也时不时。
All right, thank you.
好哒。谢谢你们。
Like, of course, I'm.
就像，当然，我是。
Not going to say don't do it,
but just like.
不是说不做，而是喜欢。
You know.
你知道。
Always consider yourselves
and always prioritise yourselves.
始终考虑自己，始终优先考虑自己。
That will make me
the I'll make me very happy
那会让我，我会让我很开心
to know, like, you're you're OK.
要知道，就像，你是你没事。
Deli, thank you for the sensor
on our subs as well.
熟食店，也感谢您为我们的潜艇提供传感器。
I pinch. Thank you for. That's all no NCR.
我捏。 谢谢你。 那完全不是NCR。
Thank you for that's on now are thank you
for being so much warm and fun for us.
谢谢你现在正在播放，谢谢你为我们带来如此多的温暖和乐趣。
I hope everybody.
我希望大家。
Enjoyed the karaoke whether it was just
by listening or the small little advancers
享受卡拉OK，无论是听听还是小小进步者或其他什么，或者我只是闲逛聊天
or whatever
or I just hang out and chat it's
it was a very fun session like.
这是一个非常有趣的会议。
This was probably one of the most funds
I've had.
这可能是我拥有的最多的资金之一。
For a karaoke session in a long time.
长时间的卡拉OK会议。
You know, like,
I fumbled a few lyrics here and there.
你知道，就像，我在这里和那里摸索了一些歌词。
I still enjoyed myself despite that
尽管如此，我仍然玩得很开心
ringer.
铃声。
And thank
you for an another for another Johnno
谢谢你的另一个约翰诺
and so we thank you for that's on
law and Moomaw.
因此，我们感谢您，因为这是法律和 Moomaw。
Thank you for the honour and the link.
感谢您的荣誉和链接。
Thank you for that download.
谢谢你的下载。
Congrats on 300 k.
恭喜300k。
Thank you so much. Link apply.
非常感谢。 链接申请。
Thank you for the big deal.
谢谢你的大事。
Now if you're so thankful and lucky
that I can be you want to kill this,
现在，如果您如此感恩和幸运，我可以成为您想要杀死它的人，我们将永远与您同在，一起看世界。
we will always stay with you
and see the world together.
No matter what happens.
不管发生什么。
You're worth all the love and support
and you're the best guild leader.
你值得所有的爱和支持，你是最好的公会领袖。
I try to.
我试着。
Be a good leader for you guys
any time I can.
任何时候我都可以成为你们的好领导。
And I mean
我的意思是
it's just the beginning, right?
这只是开始，对吗？
There is. This is just like.
有。 这就像。
What the first chapter
or the first few chapters.
什么第一章还是前几章。
We have so much more to do.
我们还有很多事情要做。
We have so many quests.
我们有很多任务。
The gone.
走了。
It's like an endless journey, right?
这就像一个无尽的旅程，对吧？
You're going to have that endless journey
together and we'll see where it takes us.
你们将一起经历那无尽的旅程，我们会看看它会把我们带到哪里。
And I'm excited to see what comes down the
line where it's take it on
我很高兴看到它所带来的结果
you. Watch Hal's moving castle.
你。 观看哈尔的移动城堡。
Two days ago, and it's such a blessing
to hear you sing this.
两天前，听到你唱这首歌真是太幸运了。
Thank you so much, Rubble.
非常感谢你，碎石。
And I love
and hope that you have a nice life.
我爱并希望你过上美好的生活。
You're amazing.
你太棒了。
OK, the promise of the world was, oh.
好吧，世界的承诺是，哦。
I don't know when I why I thought
about singing it, but I was thinking about
我不知道我什么时候想到唱它，但我在想
you know, talking about my promise
你知道，谈论我对我的，我的，我最好的朋友的承诺。
to my, my, my best friend.
My he's no longer with us,
我的他不再和我们在一起，就像我说的，但我真的
like I said, but I really do
want to sing something
that captured that feeling I wanted.
想唱一些能捕捉到我想要的感觉的东西。
So, you know, I give to you guys.
所以，你知道，我给你们。
And I think that was like
the perfect song.
我认为这就像一首完美的歌曲。
It really was.
确实如此。
To get the message through.
让消息通过。
So I'm glad you guys enjoyed Joy that are
所以我很高兴你们喜欢Joy
part of the karaoke
卡拉OK的一部分
are amazing that God, thank you for the.
太神奇了，大神，谢谢你了。
All the bits. That's a lot of bits, bro.
所有的位。 那是很多位，兄弟。
He's so much a six.
他是一个六岁的人。
Thank you for the multiple donors.
感谢您的多个捐助者。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
That's that's a lot of donors are.
那就是很多捐助者。
Ron, thank you for this honour
you undertake.
罗恩，感谢你所承担的这份荣誉。
Congratulations. That is also.
恭喜。 那也是。
The 30th. Day since you watch your show
and you are my treasure til baby.
30 号。 自从你看你的节目以来，你是我的宝贝，直到宝贝。
Well, I mean,
嗯，我的意思是，
well, I mean
好吧，我的意思是
ends are for other was your oine right.
目的是为了其他是你的权利。
Getting better and better at.
越来越擅长。
Saying that one that's it's difficult
说那是困难的
I stutter you know
我结结巴巴你知道噗谢谢你的艾滋病。 不好了。
puff thank you for the AIDS. Oh, no.
Congratulations.
You're glad to be part of the guild.
恭喜。 你很高兴成为公会的一员。
Every day of your life is full of joy
and hope and you really hope
你生活中的每一天都充满了快乐和希望，你真的希望享受和我在一起的时光，并从我的直播中学习英语。
to enjoy the time with me
and learning English from my stream.
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
Learning English
学习英语或我的朋友是最好的主意，但如果它有帮助，那么，嘿，我很高兴。
or my friend is the best idea,
but if it helps, then, hey, I'm glad it.
It's been helping
它一直在帮助
I do want to
我确实想说，比如，如果你想学习更多，你知道，英语，
say, like, if you do want to learn more,
you know, English,
I hope all your schools are teaching.
我希望你们所有的学校都在教书。
You are like you take classes.
你就像上课一样。
Have like the best.
喜欢最好的。
Ways to take classes and like,
you hit the textbook still.
上课方式之类的，你还是打教科书。
That's why I want to. Try and learn.
这就是我想要的原因。 尝试并学习。
I try and learn Japanese very soon.
我很快就会尝试学习日语。
I got to get.
我必须得到。
Go get those textbooks. Man.
去拿那些教科书。 男人。
That's the first language I'm tackling.
这是我要处理的第一种语言。
And then now I know I want to try Mandarin
as well.
然后现在我知道我也想试试普通话。
Mandarin Chinese and so
普通话等
and so what else I think
所以我认为还有什么可以再次重温西班牙语。
brush up on Spanish again.
I really do want to do more Spanish.
我真的想做更多的西班牙语。
Spanish is a fucking awesome
language, man.
西班牙语是一门非常棒的语言，伙计。
It makes sense.
这说得通。
English doesn't make sense.
英语没有意义。
The Spanish when I learnt it in
high school or like part of it, I forgot.
当我在高中学习西班牙语或其中的一部分时，我忘记了。
It just makes. Sense, man. Like it was
它只是使。 感觉，伙计。 就像它是
God bless
上帝保佑
Moyer.
莫耶。
Vonnie, thank you for the big deal.
No cuts.
冯尼，谢谢你的大事。 没有削减。
Thank you for the honour of Mommy.
谢谢妈妈的荣幸。
Mommy.
妈妈。
Thank you for the ads on his wall. Sissy.
谢谢你在他的墙上的广告。 娘娘腔。
Thank you for the five.
谢谢你的五个。
Oh, it's your own give subs
ends. Are zero.
哦，这是你自己给潜艇的目的。 为零。
Thank you for the $50.
谢谢你的 50 美元。
Congrats on 300 k.
恭喜300k。
Thank you to all the thank you so much.
非常感谢大家。
I hope you're still around.
我希望你还在。
And if you are I hope you're
having the awesome fucking night bro.
如果你是我希望你有一个真棒他妈的晚上兄弟。
Thank you for another.
谢谢你的另一个。
Hope and everybody thank you so much
希望和大家非常感谢你
lady Jemmy. Trask. Now.
杰米女士。 特拉斯克。 现在。
Oh yeah. That reminds me.
哦耶。 这让我想起了。
I don't know if to.
不知道要不要。
Shit, we got to finish that, Tony.
该死，我们必须完成那个，托尼。
Maybe I'll put that on schedule
for next week
如果我记得的话，也许我会把它按计划安排在下周
if I remember
but she's. She's dead now.
但她是。 她现在死了。
We killed her, right?
我们杀了她，对吧？
Yes. See ya.
是的。 拜拜。
See, congratulations on the day
I'll always be there with you.
看，恭喜我永远和你在一起的那一天。
Your songs are beautiful.
你的歌很美。
Yes, you are wealth. They are treasure.
是的，你是财富。 他们是宝藏。
Treasure.
宝藏。
That is what you are. Her.
那就是你。 她。
Honey, you're my golden star.
亲爱的，你是我的金星。
Yeah.
是的。
I know.
我知道。
It's a great song, man. Our Bruno Mars.
这是一首很棒的歌，伙计。 我们的布鲁诺火星。
I feel like I should sing more
Bruno Mars song.
我觉得我应该多唱布鲁诺·马尔斯的歌。
Still all. Right.
还是全部。 对。
I'm all right.
我没事。
Yeah. Yeah, I like you.
是的。 是的，我喜欢你。
Guys idea of, like, dedicating a stream
to, like, a specific genre
伙计们的想法，喜欢，专门为特定类型的歌曲和音乐提供流，所以我可能会尝试这样做。
of songs and music,
so I might try and do that.
For future karaoke, like,
you know, like rap,
对于未来的卡拉OK，比如，你知道的，比如说唱，
rap, rap, karaoke. Or.
说唱，说唱，卡拉OK。 或者。
Or K-pop karaoke or, you know, um,
或者 K-pop 卡拉 OK 或者，你知道，嗯，
just sad love songs or something
like that.
只是悲伤的情歌或类似的东西。
Stick to a theme or something.
坚持一个主题或其他东西。
Right?
对？
Oh, girl.
哦，姑娘。
Thank you for another two and give subs
谢谢你的另外两个并给潜艇
tight end.
紧张的结局。
Thank you for the 300 bits.
谢谢你的300位。
I am. Thank you for that, Donald.
我是。 谢谢你，唐纳德。
So sorry. Sorry I stay here,
but you have to go to work.
非常抱歉。 对不起，我留在这里，但你必须去上班。
I'll be over.
我会结束的。
Great. Simon, I really enjoyed
seeing listening to you sing.
伟大的。 西蒙，我真的很喜欢听你唱歌。
You're great.
你很棒。
You know more.
你知道的更多。
You thank you for listening and zahava.
谢谢你的聆听和zahava。
Wow. Have a good day at work.
哇。 祝你工作顺利。
I can't talk.
我不能说话。
Wow. I'm like, my work
哇。 我喜欢，我的工作也是。
also.
Yeah, I think a lot of people didn't know,
but I do like rapping.
是的，我想很多人不知道，但我确实喜欢说唱。
I do like rap music a lot.
我非常喜欢说唱音乐。
I listen to it a lot
when I. Go to the gym.
我经常听。去健身房。
It's like my motivation, music it's like,
这就像我的动力，就像音乐，把事情做好。
get shit done.
Rap music is awesome, and I don't.
说唱音乐很棒，我不喜欢。
I'm just. I suck at it.
我只是。 我很讨厌它。
There's like one rap from a native, sir,
that I wanted to learn.
先生，我想学一首当地人的说唱。
Those are from like a collaboration
or something like that.
那些来自合作或类似的东西。
You're more Sagar Kimmy.
你更像是 Sagar Kimmy。
Only you're more Su Sakura.
只有你更苏樱。
Keep me on my feet.
让我站起来。
Yeah, and he did it often.
是的，而且他经常这样做。
That's, you know, and
那就是，你知道，而且
it sounds like all on life.
这听起来就像生活中的一切。
Find it
找到它
just stay the same.
保持不变。
It sounds really good.
听起来真的很好。
I wish I had seen it in the past.
我希望我在过去见过它。
You know I hate you.
你知道我恨你。
Yeah, it's,
ah, it's a really intense rap, but.
是的，它是，啊，这是一个非常激烈的说唱，但是。
I feel like that is my goal, bro.
我觉得这是我的目标，兄弟。
That's like the top of.
那就像是顶部。
My list
priority of trying to cover this song
我尝试翻唱这首歌的优先顺序
with a friend in the future.
以后和朋友一起。
If I once I learn, like, you know,
get more comfortable with, like, actually
如果我一旦学会了，比如，你知道，变得更适应，比如，实际上用英语和日语做说唱，
doing rap in both, like,
English and Japanese,
not suit darker.
不适合深色。
I thank you for this honour to educate.
我感谢你有这个荣幸来教育。
Congrats all day.
恭喜一整天。
We love you and thank you for bringing.
我们爱你，感谢你带来。
Out a good. Song
出一个好。 这首歌带来了这么多，因为我希望我没看错。
bringing so much,
because I hope I read that right.
No problem.
没问题。
I, I think it was right
talking about treasure.
我，我觉得说宝物是对的。
I'm glad you guys love treasure, man.
我很高兴你们喜欢宝藏，伙计。
That's
that's really good to know. Like this.
这真是太好了。 像这样。
That was kind of like a.
那有点像一个。
You know, a curveball in the karaoke
along with Fall on my limo.
你知道，卡拉 OK 里的曲球和我的豪华轿车上的秋天。
But, yeah, i, i really.
但是，是的，我，我真的。
I'm really glad that treasure
was a favourite of many people.
我真的很高兴宝藏是很多人的最爱。
You guys are my treasure.
你们是我的宝藏。
You, Michael.
你，迈克尔。
Hui, thank you for the big tell.
辉，谢谢你的大话。
No. Oh, my God.
不，哦，我的上帝。
Thank you for the karaoke stream.
感谢您提供卡拉 OK 直播。
Not today. Only I mean every stream.
今天不行。 只是我的意思是每个流。
I'm very.
我很。
You're you love listening to me sing.
你是不是喜欢听我唱歌。
And your voice makes me relax and heal.
你的声音让我放松和治愈。
Don't be shy.
别害羞。
Your voice is very nice.
你的声音很好听。
You can't even, like,
你甚至不能，比如，
I will always. Like, be shy.
我将永远。 比如，害羞。
You know. It's hard sor
你知道。 这很难
it's hard to get over those nerves,
I guess.
我想很难克服这些紧张情绪。
Like,
像，
I to I don't think I'll.
我想我不会。
I'll ever get over those nerves.
我将永远克服这些神经。
Like it's a good thing.
喜欢它是一件好事。
Like people have that,
you know, positive stress
就像人们一样，你知道，积极的压力
before they go into like, something big.
在他们进入喜欢之前，一些大事。
It's normal.
这是正常的。
But yeah, I was just really shy
because I was worried I would
但是，是的，我真的很害羞，因为我担心我会
the songs went, like, fuck up real
歌曲去，就像，真的很难听一首歌或类似的东西。
hard on a song or something like that.
But I'm glad to know, like.
但我很高兴知道，喜欢。
You know, I didn't, I didn't blunder
anything and it went really well.
你知道，我没有，我没有犯任何错误，而且进展非常顺利。
Fiona Hannah see.
菲奥娜汉娜见。
I did it all. A couple of karaoke ago.
我都做了。 几个卡拉OK前。
Oh, nurse, thank you for the $300.
哦，护士，谢谢你的 300 美元。
Ah, congratulations on 300 k.
啊，恭喜你300k。
I promise I will stay here
as long as I can.
我保证我会尽可能待在这里。
And you shine so bright today.
而你今天如此耀眼。
Oh, oh,
哦，哦，
oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Well, that's a sweet message.
嗯，这是一个甜蜜的信息。
Well, it's
嗯，是
a shine bright that I really
一个闪耀的光芒，我真的闪耀着光芒
shine bright
I'm glad you're here.
我很高兴你在这里。
Thank you so much for the know, and
I appreciate you listening to my songs.
非常感谢你知道，我很感激你听我的歌。
I had fun with fire.
我玩火很开心。
I think the one that I enjoyed
the most was probably dry flower.
我想我最喜欢的可能是干花。
Like I said,
I got to go do more dry flower.
就像我说的，我得去做更多的干花。
Enzo, thank you for putting the stream
in the community.
Enzo，感谢您将流放到社区中。
Hypnosis like it means a lot easier.
催眠之类的意思就容易多了。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
Bunny.
兔子。
Thank you for another day now. Love you.
谢谢你的另一天。 爱你。
Love you, too.
我也爱你。
Noona.
诺娜。
Thank you for the doll.
谢谢你的娃娃。
No, Ahmad.
不，艾哈迈德。
Thank you for the doll. No.
谢谢你的娃娃。 不。
And, Mira,
thank you for that song, though.
还有，米拉，谢谢你的那首歌。
And the fat. Fox.
还有脂肪。 狐狸。
Thank you. For the doll.
谢谢你。 为娃娃。
Now, Rich, thank you for the 15 months.
现在，Rich，谢谢你这 15 个月。
Welcome back, Rich.
欢迎回来，里奇。
Hey, I got how to do on how to do.
嘿，我知道怎么做就怎么做。
And how's it going?
进展如何？
I wanted to. I don't know how it's ok.
我想。 我不知道它是如何确定的。
With the bubble,
but do but do. You'll be do be
与泡沫，但做但做。 你会的
gonna thank you for that.
会感谢你的。
Oh, no and make a
thank you for the it's on though
哦，不，谢谢你，尽管它也开启了
as well
Chyna thank you for the doll now
and keeping faith
Chyna 现在感谢你的娃娃，并坚信我们对卡拉
it's on our thanks for the karaoke baby
that's all we all love you.
OK 宝贝的感谢，这就是我们都爱你的一切。
Well I need I'll be.
好吧，我需要我会。
Cute call me that and.
可爱的叫我那个和。
So I'm going to
所以我要
grab your face and
抓住你的脸和
only thank you for the song as well.
也谢谢你的歌。
Hey, on the album,
嘿，在这张专辑上，恭喜你达到了这么多里程碑。
congrats on hitting so many milestones.
You're doing so great.
你做得很好。
And I was a love to listen to you sing it.
我很喜欢听你唱歌。
Is there of all the love.
Oh, right. I forgot.
有没有所有的爱。 啊对。 我忘了。
I will make I will publish the vide.
我会做我会发布视频。
I should publish the bottle right now.
我现在应该发布瓶子。
But for. Some reason, switch.
但对于。 有什么原因，换。
Doesn't want me like,
you know, publish the VOD
不希望我喜欢，你知道，发布 VOD
until after the stream is over
for some odd reason.
直到流结束后出于某种奇怪的原因。
So I'm going to
所以我要
I think that's just how it's set up now.
我认为这就是它现在的设置方式。
So ill girl.
这么病态的姑娘。
So you guys can listen to the
to the songs again
所以等我结束直播后你们可以再听一遍歌曲
once I end stream later
a lot of people do I have to head out?
很多人我要出去吗？
Yeah. You guys are busy days today.
是的。 你们今天很忙。
It is the morning for some of you. Right.
So have a good day.
对于你们中的一些人来说，这是早晨。 对。 所以祝你有美好的一天。
Don't don't feel pressure to stay.
All right.
不感到压力就不要留下。 好的。
Be sure to us your responsibilities
and there will always be the bad.
一定要对我们负责，总会有不好的。
Take care.
小心。
All right,
好的，
Amber, thank you for that sonar and saw
it's in the air.
琥珀，谢谢你的声纳，看到它在空中。
Think of it. It's online.
想想看。 它是在线的。
Vampire Popper, the funny name
吸血鬼波普尔，有趣的名字
oh, see?
哦，看到了吗？
That's it, shopper.
就是这样，购物者。
You've killed me.
你杀了我。
I'm on the way to the grave now.
我现在正在去坟墓的路上。
What did I do?
我做了什么？
What did I do? What I do?
我做了什么？ 我做什么？
Something bad.
It was it. The songs? I don't know.
有什么不好的。 就是它。 这些歌？ 我不知道。
Don't die.
不要死。
Please don't die. I'll be sad if you die.
请不要死。 如果你死了，我会很难过。
No, no dying.
不，不会死。
OK, I'll fucking kill.
好吧，我他妈会杀的。
You if you die.
如果你死了。
Amamou Thank you for the I'll again. Ah,
Amamou 谢谢你的我会再次。 啊，
I see he Tommy.
我看见他汤米。
Thank you for the baked on.
谢谢你的烘烤。
No, congratulations on the 300
can switch and £400 order.
不，恭喜 300 可以转换和 400 英镑的订单。
Thank you for appearing in my life
and thank you for the karaoke scream.
谢谢你出现在我的生命里，谢谢你的卡拉OK尖叫。
There's something that.
有这样的东西。
Just hit me in the heart.
只是打我的心。
And. On you when people type to thank you
for appearing in my life.
和。 当人们打字感谢你出现在我的生活中时，你会写在你身上。
That's a very sweet line. I don't know.
这是一条非常甜蜜的线。 我不知道。
It's like the equivalent of saying
thank you for existing,
这相当于说谢谢你的存在，
I guess, and analogies
means a lot to be appreciated that way.
我想，类比意味着很多值得赞赏的方式。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
My stomach just rumbled.
我的肚子刚刚咕咕叫。
I got to get food after the stream.
我必须在溪流之后得到食物。
There's a there's some food.
有食物。
Downstairs, so I got to eat that.
I did not.
在楼下，所以我得吃那个。 我没有。
Eat before the stream like a dummy
because I wanted to
像个傻瓜一样在溪流前吃东西，因为我今天只想吃一个短的。
just have a short one today.
So I will eat afterwards.
所以我以后会吃。
No worries.
不用担心。
My mom has food downstairs.
我妈妈在楼下吃饭。
Mama, thank you for this. I know, pumpkin.
妈妈，谢谢你。 我知道，南瓜。
I love you.
我爱你。
Maybe you can hear some Chinese songs
in the future.
也许你以后可以听到一些中文歌曲。
I was considering doing some, but it's
just like I don't know which ones to do.
我正在考虑做一些，但就像我不知道该做什么一样。
I remember my friends did one.
我记得我朋友做过一个。
I was called, like, warrior or.
我被称为战士或。
Something like that and saw
类似的东西，看到
I might give that a try,
我可能会试一试，所以我忘了转。
so I forgot to turn.
Alert Box is back on. Sorry about that.
警报框重新打开。 对于那个很抱歉。
I don't know what it was, but I.
我不知道那是什么，但我。
I want to try and,
我想尝试，
you know, expand the different languages
as well.
你知道，扩展不同的语言也是如此。
Like other different languages
besides our Japanese and Tsar
像除了我们的日语和沙皇之外的其他不同的语言
and Korean, which are my comforts
和韩语，这是我的舒适工作。 我唱了一首黑色粉红色的歌。
job. I sing a black pink song.
I love black pink, bro. My God,
我喜欢黑色粉红色，兄弟。 我的上帝，看饼干。
watching cookies.
K-pop inspired me to,
like, wanted to do more K-pop song style,
K-pop 启发了我，比如，想做更多的 K-pop 歌曲风格，
acoustic style.
声学风格。
Most likely.
最有可能的。
Then. Thank you for that's on our show.
然后。 谢谢你在我们的节目中。
He's amazing tonight. We love you a lot.
他今晚很棒。 我们非常爱你。
And your son scenes also come in
so you have a good night.
你儿子的场景也进来了，所以你有一个美好的夜晚。
You have a good night.
愿你有个不错的晚上。
The odds you would hope
it's not too late for you Guru.
你希望这对你大师来说还为时不晚。
Thank you for the deal. No,
and I thank you for this. I know.
谢谢你的交易。 不，我为此感谢你。 我知道。
I sure thought thank you for being a huge.
我当然认为谢谢你是个大人物。
Inspiration to me and becoming a YouTuber.
对我的启发并成为 YouTuber。
Because of you. I'm honestly.
因为你。 我是诚实的。
Trying to do the best in everything all.
力求在每件事上做到最好。
You dude I it's
你哥们我是
i, i really I'm really glad you.
我，我真的很高兴你。
Brought that up because like
提出这个问题是因为就像你们都说，喜欢，自我
you all say, like, self
helping YouTubers or not viewers
or whatever, but really, I believe in you.
帮助 YouTubers
或不帮助观众或其他任何东西，但真的，我相信你。
You got this.
你得到了这个。
I Twitter on 400 k oh it's an amazing
you I'll always be there for you and big
我在 400 k
who you love our leader.
上推特哦，你真是太棒了，我将永远在你身边，你爱我们的领导者。
Oh cut off what I weird.
哦切掉我奇怪的东西。
Right back to my other.
马上回到我的另一个。
Point though I was saying.
虽然我说的是点。
I started off.
我开始了。
As a P&G I never had you know this
作为一个宝洁，我从来没有让你知道这一点
I was just you know a pick
我只是你知道一个选择只是屏幕上的一张图片
just a picture on the screen and
going from that to
this has been quite the journey so
从那个到这个是一段相当长的旅程，所以
if it means anything, hey
I know exactly where you're coming from.
如果这意味着什么，嘿，我确切地知道你来自哪里。
I used to be,
you know, really, really small and
我曾经，你知道，真的，真的很小，而且
now I have so many wonderful
现在我有很多很棒的朋友和公会成员和我一起踏上这段美妙的旅程。
friends and guild members with me
to join me on this wonderful journey.
So I hope that.
所以我希望如此。
You can reach
你可以到达
reach that same happiness that I have.
达到和我一样的幸福。
OK, you got this. Don't don't stop.
好的，你明白了。 不要不要停止。
Don't give up.
不放弃。
Trust me, it gets better.
相信我，它会变得更好。
It will get better.
它会更好的。
I was in.
我是在。
Your shoes like a year ago, a couple of
years ago, and I know what it's like, bro.
你的鞋子就像一年前，几年前一样，我知道它是什么样的，兄弟。
So just keep it to keep at it.
所以只要坚持下去就可以了。
All right?
好的？
Are on.
在...上。
You sing very well,
and I can feel the emotions in your song.
你唱得很好，我能感受到你歌中的情绪。
Ah, I listen to your songs to sleep
every day and I have more songs.
啊，我每天听你的歌睡觉，而且我还有更多的歌。
All you guys listen to me sings.
你们都听我唱歌。
I got a better lot
当你上床睡觉时，我得到了很多你们听我说的东西。
of what you guys listen to me
when you get to bed.
Oh, my. God. That's sweet.
天啊。 上帝。 太贴心了。
I might post.
我可能会发帖。
A couple of the songs
that we did tonight on my channel.
我们今晚在我的频道上播放的几首歌曲。
Maybe we'll see, because I was a
I was proud of them.
也许我们会看到，因为我为他们感到骄傲。
Wasn't one of them.
不是其中之一。
I will see y'all.
我会见到你们的。
I'll see
我再看看吧
Keith Staples.
基思·斯台普斯。
Hasn't been long.
时间不长。
By really love coming to your streams.
真的很喜欢来到你的溪流。
Your voice is always so comforting. Oh.
你的声音总是那么令人欣慰。 哦。
My stomach is rumbling a lot.
我的肚子咕咕叫。
Sorry, and always brings
a smile to my face.
对不起，总是给我带来微笑。
Congrats on 300 K and thank you
for letting us hear you sing.
恭喜 300 K，感谢您让我们听到您的歌声。
I'm glad that you were around to hear me
sing.
我很高兴你在附近听我唱歌。
Dude, your company here, it's
listened to my songs into
伙计，你的公司在这里，听我的歌变成我的声音很
my voice is very
it's very sweet and
它很甜，而且
I hope to be able to continue
to, you know.
我希望能够继续，你知道的。
Have more. People
有更多的。 人们
come by
and enjoy themselves as much as you do.
来吧，和你一样享受自己。
Every day.
每天。
There's like always new guilties.
总是有新的罪行。
I see new guilties in the all the time
the new people are coming into this court.
在新人进入法庭的过程中，我总是看到新的罪行。
So I really hope you enjoy your time here.
所以我真的希望你在这里过得愉快。
And I'm glad to know that saw you have
been having fun for as long as you have.
我很高兴知道你一直在玩得开心。
And it's been fun, right?
这很有趣，对吧？
Because I've been having fun still.
因为我一直玩得很开心。
And so it's nice to know
that you're also having fun, bro.
所以很高兴知道你也玩得很开心，兄弟。
Key. Thank you for that honour.
钥匙。 谢谢你的荣誉。
Thank you so much, guy.
非常感谢你，伙计。
Ah, thank you for this karaoke show
and super congrats on hitting 300 k.
啊，谢谢你的卡拉 OK 节目和超级祝贺你达到 300 k。
It makes me happy to see you grow so much
and wish you the best for the future. So
看到你成长这么多，我很高兴，并祝你未来一切顺利。 所以
thank you for agreeing to be part
of the mod scene and for being such,
感谢您同意成为 mod 场景的一部分并成为这样的人，
you know, a supportive member
while still doing an amazing job bro.
你知道，一个支持成员，同时仍然做着出色的工作，兄弟。
I don't know what to say. Thank you
我不知道要说什么。 谢谢
Azita.
阿齐塔。
Thank you for the words.
谢谢你的话。
Oh no, I can't expect that
I cried a lot today.
哦不，我不能指望我今天哭了很多。
Oh no. Please don't cry.
不好了。 请不要哭。
Please don't cry.
请不要哭。
Don't cry. Ah,
别哭。 啊，不，不哭。
no, no crying.
You want.
你要。
You want to wipe your series on my jacket.
你想在我的夹克上擦你的系列。
I got you on my sleeve.
我把你放在我的袖子上。
I don't know why I use my sleeve, bro.
我不知道我为什么要用我的袖子，兄弟。
You can feel my sweet just don't cry
你可以感受到我的甜蜜只是不哭的 raqqa。
of raqqa.
Thank you for the hotel now as well.
现在也感谢您入住酒店。
He got here. Thank you for that.
他到了这里。 谢谢你。
I know
我知道
and so goal shock.
所以目标冲击。
OK, Sagar,
好的，萨加尔，
I love you so much.
我真的很爱你。
Lucky that you're my first voice.
幸运的是你是我的第一个声音。
You were your first voice.
你是你的第一个声音。
You were, bruh.
你是，兄弟。
Your that's that's fucking sweet.
你的那个太他妈甜了
Knowing like you're somebody for something
is always always means the world's
知道你是某事的人总是意味着世界的
a person. So don't take that lightly.
一个人。 所以不要掉以轻心。
I never take that lightly.
我从不掉以轻心。
Nino Mia, thank you for the.
尼诺米娅，谢谢你。
5000 bets on, you know. Mia,
thank you so much.
5000 赌注，你知道的。 米娅，非常感谢。
Dude, have you been enjoying yourself
and had a great time in the stream
伙计，你玩得开心吗，在溪流中玩得很开心
I'll do thank you for that's all.
我会感谢你的。
No ends are a come to think of it.
没有尽头是想起来的。
It's not Andre. Mikey, think of it
that's on the agenda for this.
这不是安德烈。  Mikey，想想这件事的议程。
I know you love.
我知道你爱。
Promise of the world
the most. And yes, that you're wonderful.
世界上最大的诺言。 是的，你很棒。
You know, because of that, I will try to.
你知道，正因为如此，我会努力的。
Do promise of the world again
next time, ok?
下次再许诺世界好吗？
I promise.
I will do promise of the world's
我保证。 我会做世界的承诺
yeah. It's a promise, guys.
是的。 这是一个承诺，伙计们。
All right.
好的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Promise you can't break a pinky promise.
保证你不能违背小指的承诺。
So expect that in the next karaoke stream.
所以期待在下一个卡拉 OK 流中。
Kate Couscous.
凯特库斯库斯。
Thank you for the doll.
谢谢你的娃娃。
No, my bird kitty
不，当我们听着她美妙的歌声时，我的小猫依偎着睡着了。
cuddled up and fell asleep
as we listen to her beautiful singing all.
Are you giving kitty enough seeds?
你给小猫足够的种子了吗？
Are you feeding him well or her well?
你喂他吃得好还是她吃得好？
He's also a big fan.
他也是一个大粉丝。
Of you. I'm glad.
你的。 我很高兴。
I really like it.
我很喜欢。
One of those birds,
like cockatoos, cockatiels or on parrots.
其中一种鸟类，如凤头鹦鹉、玄凤鹦鹉或鹦鹉。
Like, I like it when they sing.
就像，我喜欢他们唱歌的时候。
Like, with you or like you know, mimic
your mimic your sounds.
就像，和你一样，或者像你知道的那样，模仿你的声音。
I love birds. That's you.
我爱鸟。 那是你。
That's just super cute.
那简直是超级可爱。
I don't know if he's one of those,
but they're really adorable.
我不知道他是不是其中之一，但他们真的很可爱。
I hope he's he's well fed and happy.
我希望他是他吃得好，快乐。
Karen, thank you for the ads. Oh, no.
凯伦，谢谢你的广告。 不好了。
You have a friend
你有一个朋友在课堂上不能看这个流，但她也说祝贺。
who can't watch this stream in class,
but she also said congratulations.
Thank you.
谢谢你。
How was your friend?
你的朋友怎么样？
A great day.
很好的一天。
Did and focus on class?
是否专注于课堂？
I think they've with it's on now and yeah.
我想他们现在已经开始了，是的。
Thank you for this honour.
Congrats on three K.
谢谢你的这份荣誉。 恭喜三K。
It's your first ever.
这是你的第一次。
Donation and it was a very big one.
捐赠，这是一笔非常大的捐赠。
I love you so much.
我真的很爱你。
You really had a bad day,
but your voice cured my day.
你真的度过了糟糕的一天，但你的声音治愈了我的一天。
Thank you for the positivity.
谢谢你的积极性。
You can call me. Yeah.
你可以联系我。 是的。
Of course I can judge you.
我当然可以评判你。
Up less than.
涨不到。
Three, Lucia.
三，露西亚。
I think for. That's all.
我想为。 就这些。
No, Enzo, Lexie.
不，恩佐，莱克西。
Thank you for the bits. And you.
Thank you for the words.
谢谢你的比特。 和你。 谢谢你的话。
I know it was something Kate.
Love you all.
我知道这是凯特的事情。 爱你们。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
You do for a
thank you for this honour and support.
感谢您对这份荣誉和支持的支持。
Thank you for that.
谢谢你。
So now a puppy.
所以现在是一只小狗。
Thank you for. That's all. No,
he got any thank you for that's on are.
谢谢你。 就这些。 不，他得到了任何感谢。
You always be. Yourself.
你永远都是。 你自己。
You should be proud of yourself.
你应该为自己感到骄傲。
You will pinch your cheeks
you won't pinch my cheeks OK.
你会捏你的脸颊 你不会捏我的脸颊 OK。
Come here. Do it there. Right now.
过来。 在那里做。 现在。
There are now
现在有
going to do it.
要做。
Are going to do it or what?
是要去做还是怎么做？
Fine.
美好的。
Serenity. Thank you for the oh, no.
宁静。 谢谢你哦，不。
And our puppy. Thank you for this.
还有我们的小狗。 这次真是万分感谢。
I know.
我知道。
You're a badminton.
你是羽毛球运动员。
Player, so you're going to be parts
this being your first national.
球员，所以你将成为你的第一个国家队的一部分。
Tournaments.
锦标赛。
Whoa, that's big, dude. Congrats.
哇，好大啊，伙计。 恭喜。
And I hope you succeed in the tournament.
我希望你在比赛中取得成功。
Get first or if you don't, then that's ok.
抢先，否则没关系。
That's ok to just have fun
and do your best.
玩得开心并尽力而为是可以的。
We're all cheering you on, bro.
我们都在为你加油，兄弟。
All the other guilty still vivi
thank you for
所有其他有罪的人仍然活着谢谢你这些没有结束所有明星谢谢你的娃娃不
these are no ends all star
thank you for the doll no
thank you for healing my whole morning.
谢谢你治愈了我的整个早晨。
We also appreciate you
and thank you for existing in this world.
我们也感谢你，感谢你存在于这个世界上。
I love you all. Amy. Are
我爱你们。 艾米。 是
a sea.
一片海。
I love watching your streams.
我喜欢看你的直播。
They're always so fun and comforting.
他们总是那么有趣和安慰。
My life has definitely brightened
since I discovered you.
自从我发现你以来，我的生活确实变得光明了。
That's all I do.
这就是我所做的一切。
That's like you guys saying this.
就像你们这样说的。
Thing is is like the equivalent
of a marriage proposal.
事情就像求婚一样。
That's all I'm. Feeling on you.
我就是这样。 对你有感觉。
See this? Oh, my. God.
看到这个了吗？ 天啊。 上帝。
It's really. Sweet.
真的。 甜的。
Well, thank you for for the kind message,
and I really do appreciate
嗯，谢谢你的好消息，我真的很感激
it, man.
它，伙计。
I get me all soft already.
我已经让我很柔软了。
Or maybe that's the alcohol. I don't know.
或者也许那是酒精。 我不知道。
Is it the alcohol or is it you guys?
是酒精还是你们？
Maybe it's both.
也许两者兼而有之。
Just switch my music real quick.
只需快速切换我的音乐。
Something a little bit more chill.
有点冷的东西。
Awesome.
惊人的。
Thank you for the online show.
And thank you for that's.
谢谢你的在线节目。 谢谢你。
I know my mother likes you very much.
我知道我妈妈很喜欢你。
She said she would
love to have a son like you.
她说她很想有一个像你这样的儿子。
She would love to have a son like me all.
她很想有一个像我一样的儿子。
Is that is that bad?
有那么糟糕吗？
I what does that mean, Ellie?
我这是什么意思，艾莉？
Is she trying to say like like,
you know, those moms are like.
她是不是想说像，你知道，那些妈妈就像。
Oh, you should be like him or like, huh?
哦，你应该像他一样，对吧？
I wish I had a son like him,
and then they give you a side eye, right?
我希望我有一个像他一样的儿子，然后他们给你一个侧眼，对吧？
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道。 我不知道。
I hope she. Doesn't do that.
我希望她。 不这样做。
I hope that's not
what she's implying, bro.
我希望这不是她的意思，兄弟。
But yeah.
但是，是的。
Like me.
像我这样的。
Some. Thank you for the honour and Zulu.
一些。 感谢您的荣誉和祖鲁语。
Thank you for.
That's all. Now you're seeing as amazing.
谢谢你。 就这些。 现在你看到了惊人的。
It's been a wonderful, wonderful
time. Keep on partying.
这是一段美好、美好的时光。 继续狂欢。
I will
I will continue to blog as I see you guys.
我会在看到你们时继续写博客。
Continue to blog. Jill, Vanessa,
I thank you for the talent.
继续写博客。 吉尔，瓦妮莎，我感谢你的才华。
All of you know how happy you make us
feel.
你们都知道你让我们感到多么高兴。
It's such a blessing.
这是一种祝福。
And I hope you guys know
how happy you make me fuckers.
我希望你们知道你们让我混蛋有多开心。
Zelda
Thank you for the big donor, but $200.
塞尔达感谢您的大捐助，但要 200 美元。
Thank you for being in my life.
谢谢你出现在我的生活中。
I really love your voice,
your scream and your smile.
我真的很喜欢你的声音，你的尖叫和你的微笑。
The screams.
尖叫声。
Thank you for liking the screams.
That's part of the package.
谢谢你喜欢尖叫声。 那是包装的一部分。
I mean, you can't.
我的意思是，你不能。
You can't sort of
have me without the scream.
没有尖叫，你就无法拥有我。
Still, you know,
don't know how long your love will last.
不过，你知道，不知道你的爱会持续多久。
Bye for now.
暂时再见。
I really, really love you
more than anything else in the world of
我真的，真的爱你胜过世界上的一切
Zelda.
塞尔达。
Princess Zelda them is all that.
塞尔达公主他们就是这样。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you for the donation and I again. I
感谢您的捐赠，我再次感谢您。 一世
it means a lot.
那意义重大。
Like the not like
the screams are endearing.
喜欢不喜欢的尖叫声是可爱的。
I always look at it as, like,
just something that's just.
我总是把它看作，就像，只是一些公正的东西。
Ha ha ha.
哈哈哈。
You know, or like, oh, my God,
why do I sound like that?
你知道，或者像，哦，我的上帝，为什么我听起来像那样？
But the fact that you said, like,
you love it, it's just really. Huh?
但事实上，你说，就像，你喜欢它，它就是真的。 嗯？
It sounds like it sounds like a screeching
有时听起来像是轮胎发出刺耳的声音或海鸥的声音，但是，嘿。
tire or a seagull sometimes, but, hey.
If you like that. Then I'm glad. I'm glad
如果你喜欢这样。 那我很高兴。 我很高兴
recrimination.
互相指责。
Thank you for that, Donna.
I'll love you, honey.
谢谢你，唐娜。 我会爱你的，亲爱的。
I love you, too, bro.
我也爱你，兄弟。
Gnocchi.
汤团。
Thank you for the donor.
感谢捐赠者。
And, Kenny, thank you for the. All
还有，肯尼，谢谢你。 全部
I realised your donor.
我意识到了你的捐赠者。
Was missing an extra zero. Here you go.
少了一个额外的零。 干得好。
I think you added an extra zero
by accident.
我认为您不小心添加了一个额外的零。
Thank you for the big donation.
感谢您的大笔捐赠。
And Kenny, really
还有肯尼，真的
well, my God, guys,
好吧，我的上帝，伙计们，
a lot of there's a lot of donors tonight.
今晚有很多捐赠者。
God is OK
上帝已经可以戴上心灵刹车标签了。
to put on the mind brake tag already.
I think it's I think it's like Warren
said, right Allin.
我认为这是我认为就像沃伦所说的那样，对阿林。
Thank you for this.
Oh, no. And I do for you.
这次真是万分感谢。 不好了。 我为你做。
Thank you for this honour.
谢谢你的这份荣誉。
And you thank you for the honour as well.
你也感谢你的荣誉。
And so thank you for this honour.
因此，感谢您的这一荣誉。
Karmically that you've ever done.
你曾经做过的业力。
All five to our softball.
我们垒球的五个人。
Congrats on 400 k.
恭喜400k。
What was the number?
号码是多少？
I remember it was like 520.
我记得好像是520。
1314. Right.
1314. 对。
I get it right. I hope I did
我明白了。 我希望我做到了
kiss.
吻。
Thank you for the honour and sons and
thank you for the honour and the paper.
感谢您的荣誉和儿子，感谢您的荣誉和论文。
Thank you for another honour and Sally
thank you for the honour.
谢谢你的另一个荣誉，莎莉感谢你的荣誉。
Your personal favourite was Villain
Your singing voice is just the medication
您个人最喜欢的是恶棍您的歌声只是您消除挫败感的药物，并祝贺您将达到更多里程碑。
you secure your frustration and congrats
on all the milestones you'll hit more.
Celine, thank you so
席琳，谢谢你们，很高兴你们喜欢这个恶棍。
glad you guys like the villain and.
I try to do like the whole.
我尽量做到喜欢整体。
What's it?
它是什么？
I remembered trying to do the laugh
in the middle and not being sure.
我记得我试着在中间笑，但不确定。
Like if that was a good idea, like be
就像这是一个好主意，就像有点即兴发挥一样。
as like a little adlib.
I'll pick him off.
我会接他。
OK, it's
好的，所以我感谢你的另一个例子，也感谢你的巨大荣誉。
so I thank you for another example and
just thank you for the big honour as well.
Congrats again.
再次恭喜。
Our Guild leader ends us so proud of you.
我们的公会领袖结束了我们为你感到骄傲。
Always be by your side
I'm glad to have you guys by my side, man.
永远在你身边我很高兴有你们在我身边，伙计。
Thank you,
谢谢，
Roth. Thank you for this honour.
罗斯。 谢谢你的这份荣誉。
Time spent with
和你一起度过的时光不仅对我来说是一种祝福，而且对那里的许多女孩来说也是一种祝福。
you has not only been a blessing to me,
but also to many girls out there.
You're able to find what you're seeking
您可以在内心深处找到您正在寻找的东西，并在我的旅程中获得乐趣。
deep within your hearts
and have fun on my journey.
I hope you guys will.
我希望你们会。
Also be able to find
what you wants on this journey because,
还可以在此旅程中找到您想要的东西，因为，嘿，我们都一起进行，好吗？
hey, we're all going on this together,
all right?
So, hey,
所以，嘿，
this is not just about me,
这不仅仅是关于我，而是关于你们仍在比赛中的人。
but it's about you guys still in the game.
It's not just sore.
它不仅仅是疼痛。
It's not just mine, OK?
这不只是我的，好吗？
We're all in this together.
我们荣辱与共。
It's not a, quote,
high school musical or anything.
它不是一个，引用，高中音乐剧或任何东西。
Mystery. Thank you for the opportunity.
神秘。 谢谢你给我的机会。
Oh, thank you for the five
arts, your ones.
哦，谢谢你的五种艺术，你的。
And Mimi, thank you for the big deal.
还有咪咪，谢谢你的大事。
No. And
没有。
don't forget, Mama.
不要忘记，妈妈。
Thank you for this.
这次真是万分感谢。
I know
我知道
you have a Chinese nickname,
which is Soul Bao.
你有一个中文昵称，就是灵魂宝。
So thou shall go cheval.
所以你要去骑马。
I heard two.
我听到了两个。
There's like, different ones.
有，不同的。
She'll go on Soul Vow.
她会继续灵魂誓言。
I shall Gonzales Puppy
我要冈萨雷斯小狗
you call me baby.
你叫我宝贝。
All right. I see.
好的。 我懂了。
Uh huh.
嗯。
Oh, it's in me.
哦，它在我里面。
Yeah, I did see little intentions.
是的，我确实看到了一些小意图。
I read it earlier.
我之前读过。
ARU, thank you for the elmo.
ARU，谢谢你的 elmo。
And it seems
thank you for the till now as well.
到目前为止，似乎也感谢你。
And I guess I'll thank you
for the five liberties
我想我会感谢你的五项自由
and Zerkalo.
和泽卡洛。
Thank you for the XL.
谢谢你的 XL。
No, we love you so much.
不，我们非常爱你。
Your existence means only. There and.
你的存在只意味着。 那里和。
Means so much to us.
对我们来说意义重大。
Thank you so much for everything
and take good care of yourself.
非常感谢您所做的一切，并照顾好自己。
By the way, you can.
顺便说一句，你可以。
Can you please say.
你能说吗。
Mahalo. The cocktail hour.
马哈洛。 鸡尾酒时间。
I'm mobu oh, hey.
我是mobu哦，嘿。
What is this?
这是什么？
Mahalo.
马哈洛。
Cocktail mother.
鸡尾酒妈妈。
Hey, swag. A peanut.
嘿，赃物。 一颗花生。
Ma. Ma, Marvel.
嘛。 妈，漫威。
Has swag of.
有赃物。
You know what.
你知道吗。
All right, pugi
好吧，普吉
the leave. What?
休假。 什么？
Thank you for.
谢谢你。
The Are you ever the 100 cities?
你曾经是 100 个城市吗？
Well, thank you so much for the bits
嗯，非常感谢你的位
I really you guys.
我真的你们。
Got me say something really
embarrassing ends up and in Pigalle.
让我说一些真正令人尴尬的事情发生在皮加勒。
Yeah a little diva that's on our end Zarco
是的，在我们这边的一个小天后 Zarco
Thank you for the zone,
though, as well. OK,
不过，也感谢您的区域。 好的，
thank you for being here.
非常感谢您的到来。
I heard you were nervous
about today's karaoke stream.
我听说你对今天的卡拉 OK 直播很紧张。
I'm also nervous.
我也很紧张。
Excited and it's on a perfectly.
兴奋，它是完美的。
It's amazing.
这是惊人的。
Everything you said touched me.
你说的每一句话都触动了我。
I love you, Bilbao.
我爱你，毕尔巴鄂。
Oh, call me baby.
哦，叫我宝贝。
I'm not a baby.
我不是婴儿。
What's not a baby?
什么不是婴儿？
Unless you mean a like.
除非你的意思是喜欢。
Oh, babe, it's a baby then. Yeah, OK.
哦，宝贝，那它是一个婴儿。 是的，好的。
That's that's cool, too.
那也很酷。
All right.
好的。
I think that is
it because my stomach is telling me shop.
我想就是这样，因为我的胃在告诉我购物。
I'll go eat food right.
我会去吃饭的权利。
Now, or I'll sa I am going to die.
现在，否则我会死的。
I got some food in my tummy
我肚子里有食物
I have a pacifier asset.
我有奶嘴资产。
Yeah, I do.
是的。
I don't use it though.
我不使用它。
Now we should end it now because yeah.
现在我们应该结束它，因为是的。
I want to get some food in my belly
before I go to bed tonight.
今晚睡觉前，我想在肚子里吃点东西。
We have another stream in the morning.
我们早上还有一条溪流。
I don't know. Shit. Cancel it.
我不知道。 拉屎。 取消它。
Oh I think we should be.
哦，我想我们应该是。
Able to play still. Yeah.
还能玩。 是的。
I don't think it's going to be a problem.
我不认为这会是一个问题。
We'll be able to continue.
我们将能够继续。
So in the morning we're going to play.
所以早上我们要去玩。
Alien isolation at
外星人隔离
9 a.m.
早上9点。
EDT or it's 1 p.m.
美国东部时间或下午 1 点。
GSD, so I'll be sure to come by for that.
All right.
GSD，所以我一定会为此而来。 好的。
Also off here, join the discord.
也离开这里，加入不和谐。
If you haven't joined the discord already.
如果你还没有加入不和谐。
It's discord at the bar.
这在酒吧是不和谐的。
Dogs.
小狗。
I shop all. Right.
我都购物。 对。
Up in there. And the eight of us
在那里。 还有我们八个人
I post on when we go live and then other
announcements for upcoming streams.
我会在我们上线时发布，然后发布其他即将到来的流的公告。
So be sure. To check it out
所以请确定。 检查一下
also be sure.
也可以肯定。
To subscribe on YouTube
if you haven't already.
如果您还没有订阅 YouTube。
Since I do have a YouTube account,
I might.
因为我确实有 YouTube 帐户，所以我可能会。
I think I'll.
我想我会。
Plan the YouTube stream
for this coming week.
计划下周的 YouTube 直播。
Yeah, and I.
是的，还有我。
Don't know what we'll do.
不知道我们会怎么做。
On YouTube though. Yeah,
虽然在 YouTube 上。 是的，
and what else?
还有什么？
Papa. Papa.
爸爸。 爸爸。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Follow me on Twitter
if you haven't already.
如果您还没有，请在 Twitter 上关注我。
OK, thank you.
好的谢谢。
I'm going to go
and look for somebody to rate tonight,
今晚我要去寻找评价的人，但我要留下最后一条信息。
but I'm to leave off
with one final message.
I hope everyone here has a good night
我希望这里的每个人都有一个美好的夜晚，我希望每个人都喜欢我的歌
and I hope that everyone enjoyed my songs
and what I was able to do
with all of you tonight.
以及今晚我能为你们所有人做的事情。
I mean, I see
that this has been an amazing experience
我的意思是，我看到这是一次了不起的经历，我希望继续拥有这种感觉
and I hope to continue having this feeling
I have.
我有。
It never ends and grasp
it firmly until the ends of the earth
永无止境，牢牢抓住它，直到天涯海角
because I wants to keep this journey
going and
因为我想继续这段旅程
hope that all of you will continue
希望你们所有人在这段旅程中继续陪伴在我身边。
to be by my side
for as long as you can on this journey.
All right.
好的。
Thank you for everything God is.
感谢上帝的一切。
And I'll see you at
我会在
405 hundred K
405 百千，未来更多。
and much more in the future.
OK, I'm going to play a quick outbreak
while we look for someone straight.
好的，我会在我们寻找直人的同时快速爆发。
So give me a seconds, Barbie.
所以给我几秒钟，芭比。
Who is live?
谁在直播？
Yeah, Barbie, hold on.
是的，芭比，等等。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Overwatch two came out with Overwatch two.
守望先锋二与守望先锋二一起出现。
I know some people are playing that show.
我知道有些人正在播放那个节目。
I try out Overwatch two.
我尝试了守望先锋二。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I don't care.
我不在乎。
Who is live, who's around. It's
谁在现场，谁在身边。 它是
not a gun
不是枪
so. We can go and
所以。 我们可以去读取数据。
read the data.
Oh. Oh.
哦。 哦。
Lend us.
借给我们。
Live witness, live our scars, live.
活着见证，活着我们的伤疤，活着。
Scars playing.
伤疤在玩。
All of this is the savage.
这一切都是野蛮人。
Raid that they do in the south, huh?
袭击他们在南方做的，是吧？
OK, fox boxes us alive.
好吧，狐狸让我们活着。
You know, I haven't I've never gone
to opportunity to.
你知道，我从来没有机会去。
Read case on and.
阅读案例和。
She is an.
她是一个。
Inspiration to me and a lot of other vets
is I want to go and saw your farm.
对我和许多其他兽医的启发是我想去看看你的农场。
You know,
你知道，
you're my health Corey case on let's see
你是我的健康科里案例让我们看看
them so like oh my gosh.
他们太喜欢了，天哪。
So OK hope you guys have a good night.
所以好吧，希望你们有一个美好的夜晚。
All right.
好的。
Take care. And I'll see you next time.
小心。 我下次再见。
You are you are.
你是你是。
Bye bye.
再见。
I hope the right one through
I hope it did.
我希望正确的通过我希望它做到了。
Did it go through
有没有通过
the fuck?
他妈的？
Oh, yeah, I did.
哦，是的，我做到了。
Cool.
凉爽的。
Oh, I got it.
哦，我明白了。
My my back is so stiff from today.
从今天起，我的背就僵硬了。
I really think I like overly.
我真的觉得我太喜欢了。
Tense my, my, like,
拉紧我的，我的，肩膀和脖子，就像，一切，感觉就像。
shoulders and neck and, like, everything,
it just feels all like.
Ooh, la la la la la la la.
哦，啦啦啦啦啦啦。
You know, because of what's it
你知道，因为它是什么
from all the singing
从所有的歌声中
I love you guys.
我爱你们。
Have a good night. OK, take care.
祝你晚安。 好的，保重。
And I'll see you tomorrow for our alien
isolation.
明天见，我们的外星人隔离。
Yeah.
是的。
Mama, mama.
妈妈，妈妈。
Molly guitar a little bit about that.
莫莉吉他一点点关于那个。
You are a good, simple camera on
你是一个好的，简单的相机
my equally ready zip down.
我同样准备好了拉链。
Well, I know I stole.
好吧，我知道我偷了。
The Elmo bye.
埃尔莫再见。
Bye bye.
再见。
Now. Good night.
现在。 晚安。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I need some more tea.
我需要更多的茶。
No, my tea.
不，我的茶。
It's. He's called.
它的。 他被称为。
Him. My fucking tea.
他。 我他妈的茶。
Cold tea is always a sad day.
冷茶总是悲伤的一天。
All right. Bye bye, guys.
好的。 再见，伙计们。
Take care.
小心。